本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译创作
欢迎爱好者加入我们  www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：lncpeter   望月者   不可云   Garfield2974   哈米波青   noanothertony 校对：海因里希
后期：☆☆
■
墨西哥某地
只有无比顽固的美国佬才会来这鸟不拉屎的地方
Only a hardheaded gringo... Would come down here...
执行什么援救计划  而且居然是单枪匹马
On a rescue mission... ALL ALONE
这美国佬不肯开口说话
This gringo is not going to talk.
那就杀了他
Then kill him.
速度点  将军在等着我们呢
C'mon, the General's expecting us.
你不能用自己的枪
You can't use your gun...
用他自己的枪射杀他
...Shoot him with his.
这枪用不了
It's not working.
这兔崽子的枪连撞针都没有
This asshole's gun has no firing pin.
别管他了
Leave him.
狗狗们好久没试过自己杀死猎物了
The dogs haven't had to kill for their food in a while.
朋友  下次
Next time, amigo,
先计划好再来
plan ahead.
我真是个伪天主教徒
Oh, I'm such a bad Catholic.
才不  你就是脑子有病罢了
No, you're just sick in the head.
别忘了要拿给将军的钱
Don't forget the General's money.
那美国佬贿赂错警察了
That gringo bribed the wrong cop...
还带了一把没撞针的枪
...and brought a gun with no firing pin.
撞针在这里
"战神"  史密斯上校
追踪中
联邦警察
墨西哥另外某地
"怪头"  博斯克・拜库斯
傻蛋  我心肝宝贝呢
Where's my girl, fool?
她很好  就在那里面  她好得不得了
She cool, man. She in there. She's still fine as hell.
就这样吗  你在巴达被轰出局了吗
So that's it? Bada-bing, you out of the game?
生意都吹了吗
Done with the whole trade?
-对  -问题就在这  博斯克
- Yeah.  - Well, that's the problem, Bosco.
要么继续  要么就在墨西哥
You either keep doing that,
监狱好好呆上十五年
or you do a 15- year bid in a Mexican prison
和齐拓表兄一起
with Cheeto's cousin in there.
还是老一套  你自己收拾烂摊子吧  哥们
Same old shit. You choose how to flush the toilet, brother.
好了  吃软的还是吃硬的
That's right. Easy way or the hard way.
可怜虫
来呀
Come on!
装毛的街头霸王  靠
Okay, street soldier. Shit.
注意点  怪头  你连我这老朋友都要失去了
But watch yourself, B.A., now, you gonna lose your oldest friend here.
傻瓜
还好吗  心肝  想我吗
What's up, girl? You miss me?
我可想死你了  真的  我们分离太久了  宝贝
Because l missed you. Yes, l did. It's been too long, baby.
太久太久了
Way too long.
鬼地方
Heck of a place.
这鬼地方还真漂亮
Just a heck of a beautiful place.
这是分时使用的吗  我也想享用
ls this a time- share? l'd love to get in on this.
我很喜欢你这的圣非气氛  图克
l like this whole Santa Fe motif you got going here, Tuco.
圣非  美国新墨西哥州首府
很有亚利桑那的味道  也很有美国墨西哥人的风范  真好
It's very Arizona, very Tex-Mex. It's good. It's good.
不如我们把我六点钟方向的那人叫来
Maybe we can get the guy at my six
做一些墨西哥荷叶饼怎么样
to whip up a couple of quesadiches, you know?
"小白脸"  派克中尉
我要火星人都看得到这燃烧的火焰
l want the flames to be seen by the Martians.
美国佬
Americano, gringo.
-军队情报人员  -你在说谁
- Army lntelligence.  - Who's that?
-你啊  老兄  -不是吧
- You, man.  - No.
看来也不怎么聪明  都困在轮胎里面了
You're not so intelligent because you're stuck in some tires.
我很开心  真开心
I'm happy. I'm happy.
这再好不过了吧
Doesn't get any better than this, right?
-我定是在梦里  -是呀
- I'm living the dream.  - You are!
你不是来这里
You're gonna come here...
把我装进袋子丢出边界的吗
...to throw me in a bag across the border...
但你却在那和我妻子尽情云雨
...but instead you have sex with my wife.
首先她实在太性感了
Well, first of all, she's so hot,
而且我们两个都恨你  所以就
and we both hate you. So that's just sort of how it...
-早上好  -早上好  伙计
- Good morning!  - Good morning, man!
这才是真正的派对
Now it's a party!
-你就这点能耐吗  -这才是真正的派对  伙计
- ls that your best shot?  - Now it's a party, man!
见鬼了
Oh, hell, no.
慢慢移过去
Slide over slowly.
你是在拦路抢劫吗
You jacking me?
这算什么  太阳从西边出来了吗
What is this, opposite day?
我不是抢劫犯  但如果我不及时赶到  我朋友就会死
I'm not a thief. But if l don't reach my friend in time, then he dies.
如果你不是抢劫犯  我敢保证你也不是一个杀手
lf you ain't a thief, l guarantee you ain't a killer.
左手放开方向盘  右手松开离合器  快
Take your left hand off the wheel and your right hand off the shifter now.
你不会朝我头开枪的  大叔
You ain't gonna shoot me in the head, pops.
你自己心里清楚
You know that ain't happening.
你他妈的有病吗
What the hell's wrong with you, man?
随随便便就开枪打陌生人
You shoot a total stranger?
我都不认识你  操
l don't even know you, fool. Damn.
这点伤死不了
It'll heal, l promise.
-用这个包起来  -我知道怎么做止血带  笨蛋
- Here, wrap it in this.  - l know how to make a tourniquet, fool.
我知道那很痛  但我必须让你明白
l know it hurts, but l had to make a point with you.
你以为是这把我惹毛了吗  才不是
That ain't what's pissing me off.
是你射到我的宝贝车  这惹毛了老子
You shooting my van is what's pissing me off, man.
你脑子有病吗
What's wrong with you?
你是陆军游骑兵吗  小子
You Army Ranger, son?
大叔  小心斟酌你要说的下一句话
Be real careful of what you say next, pops.
要是敢污蔑我的队伍  就准备好被我塞进引擎箱吧
And be ready to empty that burner if you start shit-talking my battalion.
从不让我的战友失望
Never shall I fail my comrades.
英勇的向全世界宣告我就是救世主
Gallantly will I show the world that I am a specially selected soldier.
若遇到敌人  我会充满干劲
Energetically will l meet the enemies of my country.
我将在战场上把他们击败
I shall defeat them on the field of battle
因为我比他们更强
for l am better trained.
我会竭尽全力去拼
And I will fight with all my might.
汉尼拔・史密斯上校  第75游骑兵团
Colonel Hannibal Smith. 75th Ranger Regiment.
我是4营的  在佐治亚州本宁堡驻防
4th Battalion. Fort Benning, Georgia.
游骑兵总部
你是大名鼎鼎的人物  我是怪头拜库斯下士
l know who you are, sir. Corporal B.A. Baracus.
我听说是因为莫须有的罪名而被开除军籍和解除武装
l mean, it was till l was dishonorably discharged for some bullshit.
下士  我不相信巧合
l don't subscribe to coincidence, Corporal.
我相信无论表面上看起来显得多么混乱
l believe that, no matter how random things might appear,
本质上总是有计划存在
there's still a plan.
我们把他喂狗了
We fed him to the dogs.
墨西哥荒漠中
That here in the middle of the Mexican desert,
在我最需要帮助的时候
when l needed him most,
我找到了一个游骑兵伙伴
l'd find a fellow Ranger.
伙计
Boy.
现在我需要你帮我去救另一个同伴
Now, l need your help to save another.
坏消息
Bad news for you today!
你等的那个救援人员  我们都把他喂给罗威纳犬咯
This rescue that's coming, we fed him to the Rottweilers
-早在一个小时之前  -好笑的是
- about an hour ago.  - You know what's funny?
你以为你抓住我了吗
ls that you actually believe that you got me.
你真以为你杀得了我吗
You actually think you're gonna kill me.
你还能开车吗
Can you drive?
保证让你大吃一惊  长官
Better than anybody you've ever seen, sir.
以前没人知道你藏在哪里
Nobody knew where you were hiding...
以前没有情报  不过到此为止了  蠢货
There was no intel...until now, asshole.
两分钟之内  我就会去享受冰镇啤酒
In a few minutes I'm gonna be having a cold beer,
而你则烈火烧身  保重了  我的朋友
and you are gonna be on fire. Take care, my friend.
-草  泥    -不
- Alpha, Mike...  - No!
马
...Foxtrot.
好好想想吧
Think about it.
操你妈的  永别了
Adios! Mother Fu...
汉尼拔
Hannibal!
你搞什么
What are you doing?
进去
Get in!
怪头  快走
B.A., move.
真他妈的
This is bullshit!
又跑了一个
Ahora, muerto!
停下来  拜托
Stop it! Please stop!
停下来  停下来  拜托  停下来吧
Please stop! Stop it! Stop! Please stop!
你这一天过得如何
How's your day going?
这滋味肯定不好受
This is not going to taste good.
宝贝  我刚吐完
Baby, l just threw up.
你等我嚼点口香糖先
Let me get some gum. Let me just get some gum.
你看到了吗  你看到图克的脸色了吗
Did you see that? Did you see Tuco's face?
你过来的时候简直叫人难以相信
When you came over, that was unbelievable!
-你要我说多少遍  -我说你真会算时间呀
- How many times did l say it?  - The timing was perfect.
-小白  你到底要我说多少次  -那太漂亮了
- How many times did I say it, Face?  - It was so beautiful.
-我叫你干掉图克一个人就好  -啥
- I told you not to take down Tuco alone.  - What?
那啥  你
Well, you...
好吧  我很抱歉
You know what? I'm sorry.
我很抱歉  没按战神大人的意思去做
I'm sorry l didn't have the Hannibal Smith How-to Manual.
-但是我必须得行动  -你的行动闯了大祸  小白
- Okay? l had to move.  - And that move snowballs, Face.
你差点害死你自己
You almost got yourself killed.
你还差点害死我  还差点害死他
Which almost got me killed and almost got him killed.
幼稚
Five-year-old.
你看起来好诺难子
You look like you got a real bad attitude.
啥
What?
我有开枪打坏你的车吗
Did I shoot up your van?
我穿走了你最中意的衬衣吗
Am I wearing your favorite shirt?
这是你最中意的衬衣吗
This is your favorite shirt?
是的  靓仔  这件就是
Yeah, pretty boy, that's my favorite shirt.
你还为我挨枪子了吗
Did you get shot for me, too?
-车还被抢了  -我抢的
- And carjacked.  - By me.
等下  他抢了你车还让你充当司机
Wait, and he still got you to drive?
多谢了  我是派克
Thank you. Peck.
我是拜库斯  没什么
Baracus. It's all good.
看到了吧  小白  这就是没有按计划来的下场
See, Face, this is what happens when we forget about plans
盲目开火
and just fire blind.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我又不是圣贤  咋能不犯错
I'm so sorry that l have feelings for a human being,
-我爱上一妞  -爱
- that l fell in love.  - Love?
等等  那三周前那个克罗地亚妞呢
Wait a minute. What about Miss Croatia three weeks ago?
满足生理需要而已
Rescue sex.
我只是想救她
l was just trying to save her.
-救她  -嗯哼
- Save her?  - Yeah.
救她吗  怎么救
Save her? How?
得了  你有什么计划  说来听听  小白
Please, do share with us your plan, Face.
好吧  我还没想过什么计划
Okay, I hadn't thought about that yet.
我就说吧  最后还得我来
Exactly. I had to.
她的飞机票
Her plane ticket.
工作签证和新的护照
Her work visa and her new passport.
别跟我说些为了救她之类的蠢话  小白
And don't bullshit me that this was about her, Face.
这只是为了干掉图克
This was all about Tuco.
还有弹夹吗
Do you have a mag?
墨西哥
美国陆军医院
索诺拉
保罗圣维森特医院
-麦克  -头儿  你怎么了
- Mike.  - Boss man. How the hell are you?
-还在这满天尘土中活着呀  -很不走运吧
- Still chewing the same dirt?  - I am, unfortunately.
-大老远的来到美丽的墨西哥  -不错
- And out here in lovely Mexico.  - Good.
-你有什么给我  -我安排了精干人员在附近盯着
- So what have you got for me?  - I got a fast bird doing pizza runs.
-行动代号是赛蒂斯之斧  -斧头吗  好
- The call sign is "Hatchet."  - Hatchet. Okay.
就是个名字而已
And that is whatever you want it to be.
这是给你的
This is yours.
不需我提醒你  他们不能到了美国佬手中
General, may I remind you, they don't take to the gringos.
我欠你个人情
I owe you one, okay?
-快快上路吧  -三年都等了
- Let's not wait till Bragg again, huh?  - Three years.
-还有孩子  想你哦  -怪头  -怎么了
- And the kid. Still you and the chicks.  - B.A.  - What?
我怎么能就这样丢下我的心肝宝贝
How am l gonna just leave my girl like this, after all that?
我可是大打出手才把她抢回来
l had to fight to get her back.
取下车钥匙  到时再回来取她
Leave the keys and we'll come back for her. Come on.
看着好破烂呀
Looking shabby.
-怎么打  伙计  -遇佛杀佛
- What is the deal, brother?  - Shoot anything that moves, okay?
-这比在哥伦比亚还糟  -我了解图克  伙计
- This is worse than Colombia.  - I know Tuco, man.
别担心  我会带她到圣特鲁佩斯的军事学院
Don't worry about it. I'll take her to war college in Saint Tropez.
我会把他们所有人全引来  别有后顾之忧
I'll get you all their numbers, so don't worry about it.
-小白  照顾下怪头  -好
- Face, look after the Corporal.  - Yeah. Okay.
有意思的是  你全身上下都是汽油味
And you're covered in gas, which I think is interesting.
去找大夫看看你的伤  下士
Find a treatment room, Corporal.
赶紧的  我去找我们的飞行员
Make it quick. I'm gonna find our pilot.
大夫  你有空来看看这个伤者吗
Hey, Doc, you got a second for a wounded vet?
小疯魔  默多克上尉
花瓶战斗机飞行员
Highly decorated combat pilot.
但你问他  他绝对会说自己最出色
You ask him, he thinks he's the best in the world.
但他是个还有点用的疯子
But he's a functioning lunatic.
上周他想修好一辆救护车用来逃跑
Last week he tried to escape by jump-starting an ambulance.
完毕
Clear.
见鬼
Damn it!
我就喜欢这种人
My kind of guy.
差点就刺到你的纹身了
lt almost hit your tattoo there.
有人见到默多克先生吗
Has anyone seen Mr. Murdock?
-旧式游骑兵纹身  -默多克先生
- The old Ranger tat.  - Mr. Murdock?
要是我说我也有  你会觉得我疯了吗
Would you think l was crazy if l told you l had one of these?
你看错了
Something wrong with your eyes, man.
-默多克先生  -我在给病人缝合伤口呢  护士
- Mr. Murdock?  - Not while I'm operating, nurse.
-别吵我  -你怎么从病房里跑出来了
- Not now.  - Why are you off the ward?
有人放屁了吗  是你吗
ls that gas? ls that you?
-我闻到了  -病房是什么意思
- l smell gas.  - What do you mean, "ward"?
-什么病房  -他是这里的病人
- What ward?  - This man is a patient here.
是你吗  别听她的  她疯了
ls this you? Don't listen to her, she's crazy.
老实说  我还是霍普金斯大学的实习医生呢
Honestly, I'm a practicing doctor at Johns Hopkins University.
你叫他给你缝成闪电状的吗  -根本没呀
- Did you ask him to do a lightning bolt?  - I asked for no lightning bolt.
-我要叫保安  -这个疯子
- I'm calling security.  - What's wrong with this fool?
-他疯了吧  -你才疯了
- Is he crazy?  - It is you.
-你着火了  兄弟  -啥  搞什么
- You on fire, man.  - What? What's that?
-搞毛  -天呀
- What the...  - Oh, Jesus!
-我太喜欢你们游骑兵了   -你脑子注水了吗
- You Rangers. I like you!  - Are you crazy?
喂  住手
Hey! Hey, come on!
下士  退后
Corporal, off. Back off!
这里可是医院
This is a hospital.
-大家都见过默多克先生咯  -何止见过
- Everybody's met Mr. Murdock.  - Met him?
他还在我手臂上纵火
He lit my arm on fire.
他还把我的伤口缝成闪电状
He stitched a lightning bolt in mine, man.
看着我  小子
Look at me, son.
据说你是个超棒的直升机飞行员
I'm told you're a hell of a chopper pilot.
是最好的  长官
The best, sir.
我才不坐这疯子开的直升飞机
I'm not getting on a chopper with this nut job.
好极了  他也是你计划的一部分吗
Yeah, that's a good... ls he another one of your projects?
我是货真价实的战士  我是个游骑兵
I'm a real soldier. I'm a Ranger, baby.
压力真大
I'm worried!
我真是个游骑兵  长官
I'm a Ranger, sir.
这对我来说就足够了
That's good enough for me.
你被我们接管
You have been released into our care
-并恢复上尉军衔  -这对我来说太不爽了
- and reinstated, Captain.  - I'm not even close to good with that.
谢谢你  长官
Thank you, sir.
我们离开这鬼地方吧
Let's get the hell out of here.
你这魅力无穷的破烂呀
You gorgeous old rust bucket, you.
想我没有
Did you miss your daddy?
小白  知道计划万无一失  最重要的是什么吗
Face, what's the most important part of a well-oiled plan?
要占据先机
To be one step ahead of the enemy,
-而不是落荒而逃  -谁说我们要逃跑了
- not to be running away from him.  - Who says we're running?
什么  我们要和那疯子
What, we're going to go in this dinosaur
-一起钻进这骨灰级灰机里吗  -嗯哼
- with this freak show?  - Yep.
你把我迷得团团转  团团转
You spin me right round, baby Right round
-螺旋翼没问题  长官  -这家伙到底是谁
- Rotors are good, sir.  - Who is this guy?
快点  我们走
Come on! Let's go!
干掉美国佬
We've got gringos to kill!
默多克  把这玩意弄上天去
Murdock, get this thing in the air.
抓紧咯
Hold on, boys!
我要试试在卡通里看到的把戏
I'm gonna try something l saw in a cartoon once.
你说卡通是毛意思  快把我们弄走
What you talking about cartoons for? Get us the hell out of here!
六点钟方向有敌方直升机
We got a hot chopper to your six.
金刚罩  你们打不到我  打不到我
I'm blocking bullets. We're bulletproof.
金刚罩  打不到我
We're bulletproof, boys!
小心
Oh, heads up.
我看见你了  美国佬
I see you, gringo!
你把我的心肝宝贝压成了薄饼  我要杀了你这混蛋
You pancaked my van! I'm gonna kill you, fool!
你不能停在那里  那是残疾人专用的
You can't park there. That's a handicap zone.
-我就知道你是个疯子  神经病  -我已经后悔了
- l knew you was crazy! l knew...  - This is a mistake.
开火
Fire! Fire! Fire!
把他们打下来
Blow them out of the sky.
我从来没有这样试过
I've never tried this before!
你看到了吗
Did you see that?
你看到他让直升飞机做空翻了吗
Did you see how he turned the helicopter?
这空对空作战真刺激  是不  老兄
Whoa! There's nothing like some good air-to-air combat, eh, boys?
别看我  看前面
Don't look at me! Look there!
他只剩热感导弹了
He's only got heat seekers left.
上尉  把我们弄走
Captain, get us out of here.
抓紧了  这可不好受
Hold on, this could get ugly!
准备好  加油啊  宝贝  继续爬升
Here we go! Come on, baby, climb!
发射导弹
Fire the missiles.
哇哇  导弹  来吧
Whoa! Missiles! Come on, come on.
这就是对付热感导弹的方法
That's how we deal with heat seekers, chaps.
我们熄火
We go cold.
搞毛
What the hell?
小白  快把他弄进来
Face, get him in here!
妈了个逼的
Holy, shit! Oh, shit!
抓住他了
Got him!
重启
Restart. Restart.
关好门
Close the door!
我知道你是空降兵  但那也太夸张了吧
l know you're Airborne Rangers, but that was ridiculous!
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
头儿  我们是要杀了图克  不是被杀
Boss, the idea is to kill Tuco, not the other way around!
抢先一步并不是计划  小子
One step ahead of the game isn't a plan, kid.
而是要抢先两三步
Two to three steps ahead.
抢在敌人出招前就将其拿下
Beating an enemy's move before it's even made.
这才是计划
That's a plan.
斧头  斧头  瞄准尾随我的目标
Hatchet, Hatchet, lock on my LC.
图克将军  你现在正未经许可
General Tuco, you are currently engaged
对美国军事人员发动攻击
in unauthorized warfare on United States military personnel.
滚你妈的  是你先挑起来的
No, no, no, no, no, no, no! You engaged me.
重复一遍
Repeat.
你现在正未经许可对美国军事人员发动攻击
You are engaged in unauthorized warfare on United States military personnel.
而且还在美国领空
Over United States air space.
-什么 - 草  泥
- What?  - Alpha, Mike...
马
Foxtrot!
-换句话说  操  你  妈  -不
- ln other words, Adios! Mother- fu...!!  - Oh, no.
干得漂亮  上尉
Well done, Captain.
-酷毙了  -酷个屁
- That was awesome.  - That wasn't awesome.
-你真是个天才  -老子死也不坐飞机了
- You are a genius!  - I'm never flying again in this thing!
相信你果然没错  头儿
l never should have doubted you, boss!
凡事都在计划之中  小子
There's a plan in everything, kid.
我就爱计划圆满的那一刻
And I love it when a plan comes together.
天龙特攻队
八年
八十次成功任务之后
前线作战基地  猎头
美军撤离伊拉克前最后的日子
没有比这更好的烹饪了
Gunpowder cooking. Nothing like it.
小白  你想要用凝固汽油红烧还是用原子弹油炸
Face, you want it napalmed or nuked?
原子弹油炸
Nuke it.
油炸
Nuke it!
默多克  他妈的给我煮熟一点
Murdock, burn the hell out of it,
给我狠狠地烧
like it was damned.
把整个地方都烧了算了  兄弟
Burn the whole place down, buddy.
阿帕奇   武装侦察直升机
-你要私家秘调酱汁吗  -不不不  不要防冻剂那玩意
- You want secret sauce?  - No, no, no. None of that anti-freeze.
秘密就是  你有病  地球人都知道
The secret's out. You crazy. Everybody knows.
没人能学会你的防冻腌泡汁  默多克
No one can do an anti- freeze marinade like you can, Murdock.
但我上次吃了以后就面瘫了
But l got a little Bell's palsy last time l ate that.
只是局部面瘫而已  来吧  有点男人样
It's only partial paralysis. Come on, take it like a man.
是的  长官  正要准备和他们对话
Yes, sir. I'm having that conversation right now.
一定会让他们明白的  一切都在我掌控  长官
We will enforce that. I've got it well in hand, sir.
我想你也不希望我局部面瘫地上战场吧
I don't think you want me to be in the field partially paralyzed, bud.
有客人哟
Visitors.
说真的  我还真吃了一惊
Wow, I'm a little taken aback. I'm not gonna lie.
中尉
Lieutenant.
很抱歉  我是不是也要叫你中尉
Oh, I'm sorry, am l supposed to call you Lieutenant back?
不  你得叫我上尉
No, you're supposed to call me Captain.
上尉
Captain. Captain?
没错
That's right.
让我想起吃的了  瞧瞧你
Captain Crunch. Look at you. Wow.
餐厅名
怪不得你不要孩子  也不要家庭
So, l guess you said no to the kids, no to the family.
就是要平步青云啊
Just no ladder you can't climb, huh?
不  亲爱的  我只是不要你而已
No, no, honey, l just said no to you.
你好呀  我叫珀西
Hello. My name's Percy.
要吃猪肉吗
Would you like some pork?
我要是把你丫手打折了  你还能再傻逼一点么
lf I broke every bone in your hand, could you still do that?
太不可思议了  三年了
This is crazy. Three years?
我们三年没见面了
We haven't seen each other for three years,
你就是来谈这个的吗
this is what we're gonna talk about?
那你想谈什么
What would you like to discuss?
乡村音乐泰斗
我那张斯蒂利・丹的CD带来了么
Did you take my Steely Dan CD?
我都懒的搭理你
I'm not even going to respond to that.
我们一口气听了九遍
We listened to it, like, nine times in a row.
品着那难喝的解百衲葡萄酒  记得吗
We were drinking that crappy cabernet. You remember that?
我们还干了点儿别的  咱干什么了
We were doing something else. What were we doing?
你还记得吗  干什么了  在卧室里
Do you remember what it was we were doing? It was in a bedroom.
你都忘了吗
You don't remember?
我只记得我离开了你
The only thing I remember is leaving.
这是我对你最美好的回忆
Which is my fondest memory of you.
你们是最棒的  可别给我惹事
You guys are the best. Stay out of trouble, you hear me?
保重  谢谢
Take care. Yes. Thank you.
头盔戴牢了
Keep that on.
上校  我叫林奇  中央情报局的
Colonel, my name is Lynch, I'm with Central lntelligence.
在之前第一次"沙漠风暴"行动时遇见一个中情局的人也叫林奇
l knew a company man named Lynch back in the first Desert Storm.
对  我们那有一堆人叫都叫这名儿
Yeah, l come from a long line of Lynches.
有想过人们为何不信任中情局吗
You ever stop to consider that maybe the reason nobody trusts the CIA
因为没人知道你们的真名
is because nobody knows your real names?
有什么可效劳的吗  林奇先生
What can l do for you, Mr. Lynch?
我要你帮我阻止萨达姆的前任手下
I need you to help me to stop Saddam's former flunkies
在未来的30小时内窃取数十亿美元
from stealing over a billion dollars in the next 30 hours.
现今我国境外唯一一个印制美元的铸币厂
Now, the only mint outside of the U.S. capable of printing our money
在伊朗境内
belonged to the Shah of lran.
曾在两伊战争期间失踪
During the lran- lraq War, it went missing.
流言盛传是萨达姆偷去了
Rumor was, Saddam had stolen it.
"沙漠风暴"时我们已经偷了回来
And we stole it back during Desert Storm.
但是没拿回模板
Well, you didn't get the engraving plates.
那不要紧
It didn't matter.
他们要想印钞票就得重建铸币厂
They would have had to rebuild a mint just to print those bills.
没错  长官
Well, sir,
他们正在这么干
it's happening as we speak.
这群阿拉伯来的暴徒占用了废弃的伊拉克国家铸币厂
Fedayeen thugs have seized what's left of the lraqi National Mint
印制了几十亿非法美国货币
to run off billions of dollars in unbacked American currency.
他们要如何把模板和十亿美钞
How are they planning on moving the plates and a billion dollars
-运出巴格达  -装甲车
- out of Baghdad?  - Armored convoy,
由退伍的伊拉克特种兵驾驶
manned with former lraqi spec ops.
速度奇快  遇佛杀佛
You know, high speed, shoot-to-kill types.
你打算怎样阻止他们
So how do you plan on stopping them?
听着  最近有流言说萨达姆的党羽
Listen, there's some rumors about some top-secret plates
要把一些高度机密的模板偷运出城
being smuggled out of the city by Saddam loyalists.
你听说了吗
Do you know anything about this?
你听好了  要是你想借此事大显身手
Seriously, if you're going to make a play for these plates,
我可得请你滚蛋了
I'm waving you off right now.
因为那是我的职责  我能搞定
'Cause it's my responsibility and it's my ass.
我是认真的
I'm serious.
小白
Face?
不然我把你告上军事法庭
l will court-martial you.
-好吧  -嘿
- Whoo! Okay.  - Hey.
别拿我的话当耳边风
Get the memo.
记得告诉你家亲爱的史密斯上校他妈的给我离巴格达越远越好
Tell your beloved Colonel Smith and stay the hell out of Baghdad.
你
You know,
你再也没回来  我以为你会回来
you never came back. l thought you were gonna come back.
我现在不是回来了么
Well, this is me, coming back.
你觉得那几个小丑真敢插手
You think those clowns can really pull this off?
听着  这话我从来说不出口
Listen, listen, l would never tell him this,
但他们确实是四个分队里最牛逼的小组
but they are the best CIAndestine unit in the four branches,
而且最擅长那些不可思议的任务
and they specialize in the ridiculous...
我去找其他人
...shadow peck and the rest of them.
-给我盯紧了他们  -遵命  长官
- Do not let them out of your sight.  - Yes, ma'am.
"暗黑破坏神"是恶魔的意思吗  -当然啦
- Doesn't diablo mean "devil"?  - Yeah, man.
去你娘的  汉尼拔  你想要我怎么样
God damn it, Hannibal, what do you want me to do?
罗素・莫里森将军
基地指挥官
如果这是我的行动
If this were my operation and you wanted it,
-那你随便插手  可这不是  -你竟让"黑森林"执行这任务
- you would have the mission.  - You let Black Forest deploy on this,
这是国际性事件  我向你保证
and it's an international incident, l promise you.
他们根本不算是士兵
They're not soldiers.
就是群混在军队里的纨绔子弟
They're frat boys with trigger fingers.
-谁指挥地面部队  -布拉德・帕克
- Who's running the ground team?  - Brock Pike.
帕克
Pike.
他就是个搞笑的暴徒  得了吧
He's a thug. He's a cartoon character. Come on.
汉尼拔  我们有命令在身
Hannibal, we have been ordered, ordered, mind you,
明确要你别靠近巴格达
to stay out of Baghdad.
-就这么定了  不得违抗  -将军
- Cut, dried, the end.  - General,
我们得给他点回旋余地  您觉得呢
we should find him a little wiggle room, don't you think?
我还认识一个叫林奇的中情局走狗
You know, l knew another Lynch, a CIA stooge.
68年时驻扎在老挝
Stationed in Laos, '68.
-和我没关系  -真的吗
- No relation.  - Are you sure?
我一看你就想起他
'Cause you remind me of him.
我几小时后得赶到喀布尔
I'm due in Kabul in a few hours.
希望我48小时后回来时已经万事大吉
I'll be back here in 48. I'm assuming we're green and go.
要是干砸了别忘通知我
Notify me otherwise.
他在总部还穿着防弹衣
He's wearing body armor in the HQ.
能看出中情局的都什么货色了吧
And that should tell you everything you need to know about the CIA.
老罗   现在没其他人了  咱们谈谈
Russ, let's do some good on the way out the door here.
那些模板的危害性太大
Those plates are gonna do all kinds of damage.
让我去搞定
Let me go get them.
算了吧  汉尼拔  这次你要置身事外
Forget about it, Hannibal. Steer clear of this one.
不要插手
Well clear of it.
这次行动是直刺萨德尔城的心脏
This is a gauntlet run right through the heart of Sadr City.
萨达姆・侯赛因是个公认的疯子
Saddam Hussein was a certifiable madman,
但还没疯狂到
but even he wasn't crazy enough
三十年后再去那地方
to go into that place more than once in 30 years.
我们一周前撤离   那里已经无法无天了
We pulled out of there a week ago and already it's the Wild West.
你听上去还是很担心的
You actually sound worried.
你还是生气了
And you actually seem offended.
不是说你不如当年了
Well, this isn't about you losing a step now.
我想你要明白这一点
l want you to know that.
我可比当年强大得多
I'm 10 times the man l was when you met me.
也迅捷得多
And twice as fast.
老罗
Russ,
我和弟兄们保证能全身而退
the boys and l can get this done, minus the bloodshed.
那些模板的危害性太大
Those plates can do all kinds of damage.
别逼我求你
Don't make me beg.
我不想看到你求人
I'd hate to see you beg, Hannibal.
你和我是这么多年的老朋友
You've been my friend for a long time.
更重要的是
More importantly,
你和那些小伙子们可能是
you and those boys have possibly been
我调遣过的最有价值的战斗力
the most valuable military asset l have ever had at my disposal.
你请求我别逼你求我
Now, you asked me not to make you beg.
但其实是我得求你
Right now, I'm begging you.
汉尼拔  求你了  这次你就放手吧
Hannibal, please, let this one go.
老罗   事关重大  不能让那帮笨蛋上呀
Russ, this is too big an enterprise. We can't let these bozos do this.
事关重大呀
It's way too big.
你是否愿意带着我的祝福出战
And you'd do it with or without my blessing?
我不会不带的
No, that I wouldn't.
我需要你的祝福
l need your blessing.
我不敢肯定这算不算是种祝福
I'm not so sure that it is a blessing.
祝你马到功成  伙计
Good hunting, my friend.
谢谢
Thank you.
和老家伙谈的如何
How'd it go with the old man?
都是些陈词滥调   你手上是什么
Same old, same old. What you got there?
我的新欢
Pictures of my new baby.
不错呀  眼光不赖
Oh, look at her. Who's a proud papa?
这些是默多克近距离拍下的
These pictures are the closest Murdock gets to that van.
等我回到洛杉矶  它就会在那儿等我了
It's ready for me when I go back to LA.
听着  怪头  我们得多待一阵子了
Listen, B.A., we're extending our stay a little bit.
得回巴格达去
We're going back into Baghdad.
上头不是命令咱别去巴格达吗
l thought we was ordered to stay out of Baghdad.
-没错  可我   -史密斯
- That's true, but I'm...  - Smith.
-帕克  -我听说你和你手下
- Pike.  - l understand you and your grunts
要抢我饭碗  我可不太高兴
are now stealing my gigs. l don't like that.
我以为你们"黑森林"大军忙着
I figured you Black Forest guys would be busy
在哪搞独裁或推翻民主呢
installing a dictatorship or overthrowing a democracy somewhere.
现在是周末  那些事得上班时间处理  大叔
It's still the weekend, yet. That's nine-to-five stuff, pops.
看看你们这群小丑
Look at you clowns.
你们算哪门子士兵
You're not soldiers.
简直就是穿着马球衫的刺客
You're assassins in polo shirts.
你们折腾一年的活儿  我们一周就能拿下
We'll make in a week what you guys make in a year.
钞票买不来勇气  小子
Cash don't buy guts, kid,
也买不来智慧
or brains.
可惜你两样都缺
And you're short on both.
这是莫里森的基地  赶紧滚出我的地盘
This is Morrison's base. Bug out of my op.
怪头  你都穿上黄色领骑衫了呀
They make you wear the yellow shirt there, B.A.?
你名字是啥意思   废物的意思吗
What's that stand for, "Barely Able"?
让开  废物
Get out of my way, punk.
别怕他们
Hey, don't sweat them.
他们可帮我们大忙了
They might have just done us a favor. A big one.
看   只剩一辆中型坦克了
Let me see, we got one medium tank left.
我跟你说  她不会平白无故地回来
I'm telling you, there's a reason she came back.
小白  我都说了  忘了她
Face, l told you, forget about her.
这女人的野心简直
The levels of ambition on this woman...
打死我也不坐飞机了  汉尼拔
I ain't stepping foot in any type of aircraft, Hannibal.
不论是滑翔机  纸飞机  还是轻型机
No gliders, paper planes, ultra-lights.
-你就是揪着这事儿不放吧  -没错
- You ever gonna let me live that down?  - No.
墨西哥那都多久前的事了  我还救了你的命
Mexico was a long time ago, and l saved your life.
那你怎么不谢我在医院里没揍烂你菊花
How about thanking me for not whooping your ass at the hospital?
没遇见你之前我是空降兵
l was an Airborne Ranger until l met you.
可你吓得跟什么似的
And you chickened out just like...
-263次跳伞  -你就不能谢谢我吗
- 263 jumps.  - Just a thank-you would have been nice.
可坐过一次你开的直升机后全毁了
And one helicopter ride with you screws it up.
空降兵却恐飞  就是个棒槌
Airborne Ranger with a fear of flying. Like a punk!
怪头  我保证  咱抢过卡车
B.A., for the last time, nobody leaves the truck
后就都在里面呆着  好吧
once we take it over. Okay?
我老表带我来到这个派对  在那里有个超棒的伴奏乐队
My cousin takes me to this party where this amazing cover band
演奏了鞭挞金属版的莱昂纳尔・里奇的怀旧金曲
does this trash metal version of Hello by Lionel Richie.
-哦  -唱起来就像这样
-Yeah. -Yeah. It goes...
嗨  你是在找我吗
Hello, is it me you're looking for?
伙计们   他们在里面多久了
Guys, how long have they been in there?
-三小时了  -三小时
- About three hours. - Three hours.
三小时
Three hours?
在里头三小时了  没出来吗
They've been in there for three hours? They haven't come out at all?
都没人出来尿尿或其他什么的吗
No one came out to take a leak, nothing?
一个也没
- No.  - Nope.
我站这儿才一会儿就已经感觉不对了
I've been here for three seconds and that sounds odd to me.
我就像猎鹰般的盯着他们
I've been watching that tent like a hawk.
是吗  我怎么看到你们只是坐这儿吃意大利肉汁烩饭
Really? lt looks like you're eating some risotto and sitting on your ass.
我不知道了  我想来点汤
I don't know. I wanted the soup.
-我吃的不是意大利肉汁烩饭  -真不是
- I wasn't eating risotto. I had... -It's not risotto.
伙计们
Yeah, boys.
他想挑事呀
Yeah, he wants to fight, doesn't he?
靠这也太爽了  还给我们找了跳脱衣舞的妞呀
Damn, this is awesome. They got us a stripper, too.
你眼神就像我们当兵的一样性感  比如说我
You got that hot enlisted look. Me likey.
在我关你们禁闭之前  我想知道  他们哪去了
Before l throw you in the stockade, where are they?
没跟我们说哦  上尉
They didn't tell us... Captain.
只给了我们一箱啤酒和每人五十块
They just gave us a case of beer and 50 bucks apiece.
给我的是一百
I got a hundred.
给你的是一百块呀
Oh, did you get a hundred?
这假发是不是归咱们了
You think we get to keep the hair?
策划  行动  部署
Staging, movement, action plan.
你们有得读了
There's a nice read for you.
太给力了  汉尼拔  要的就是这个
Hell, yeah, Hannibal. This is it right here.
让人难以置信
This is bat-shit insane.
-完美  -头儿  太疯狂了
- It's perfect.  - This is beyond nuts, boss.
习惯就好
It gets better.
怪头  你去找一块和你块头差不多大的金属做滑板
B.A., you'll need a piece of contoured metal to make a skid plate.
快走  傻瓜
Let's go, fool.
默多克  去弄块车用电池
Murdock, we'll need a car battery, too.
看看"黑森林"那群傻帽那边有不
See if the boys at Black Forest can help us out.
我们还需要记者证
Press credentials, we need them.
到媒体中心的帐篷里去找找
Hit the media tent and see what's lying around.
抱歉  伙计  我看你
Sorry, my friend, l see you've put
刚把南非电视台的话筒放下边了
the South African microphone at the bottom.
你不能总让CNN高高在上
You can't always put the CNN on top.
当兵的  这儿有两个话筒  我不清楚是
Private, there are two mics. I don't know if there is something...
早先我曾是个帅小伙
I was a moving man in my younger days
默多克  我们得弄台新闻摄影机
Murdock, we need a news camera.
就看你的了
See what you can do.
抱歉  抱歉
All right, sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
你好  我
Hello. I'm...
我爱上你了
I'm in love with you.
听着  我们正在做预备性会谈
Listen, we're doing a preliminary poll of...
是关于那个什么  对了  撤军
What are we talking about? Of the pull-out.
还需要气囊  越多越好
We're gonna need airbags, lots of them.
-你是哪个部门的  -法国世界报
- What bureau are you with, darling?  - Le Monde.
你是法国人
Are you French?
你好  我是帕克尔将军  我需要
Hello, this is General Parker. I need...
找你的
Okay. It's for you.
要进行空袭  你自己去和上头说
Hey, fool, you need to call an air strike on yourself.
-我们这没问题了  老兄  再会  -不  我们得回去
- We're good, mate. I'll meet you.  - No, I think we need to get going now.
你给我听清楚了
You need to understand what I'm telling you right now.
怪头  弄块磁铁
B.A., we're gonna need a magnet.
要磁力够强的
A powerful one.
看过蓝人乐队的演出吗
You ever seen Blue Man Group?
其他的交给我
I'll pick up the rest.
我想冒次险
I'm just gonna go for it.
你愿意付出一切  换取这个机会吗
What would you give for one chance
那就是回来大声告诉我们的敌人
to come back here and tell our enemies
他们也许能夺走我们的生命
that they may take our lives,
却永远夺不走我们的自由
but they'll never take our freedom!
恶搞《勇敢的心》
准备好进城了吗
Ready to go downtown?
祝君好运
Good luck.
-谢谢  -让他们见鬼去吧
- Thank you.  - Give 'em hell.
莫里森将军  汉尼拔・史密斯在他妈哪儿呀
General Morrison, where the hell is Hannibal Smith?
上尉   和首长说话要礼貌
Captain, you would do well to revise your tone and readdress me.
将军  我奉命可以随时取代你
General, I have authority under DClS that supersedes your command,
为免难堪  我最后再问你一次
so last time, before this becomes embarrassing for the both of us,
汉尼拔在哪儿
where is Hannibal Smith?
你先出去下  将军
Would you excuse us, General?
上尉  我从军快四十年了
Captain, in nearly 40 years of being in this army,
已经不是刚当兵时的火爆脾气了
I have learned to control my temper
特别是对待下属时我更会和和气气
and my voice when in the presence of a subordinate officer
现在到底是谁他妈的说话这么不客气
who, for at least the time being, seems to have lost her goddamn mind.
我理解是
Now, it is my understanding
你有事要问我  对吧
that you have a question for me. ls that correct?
是的
You are correct, sir.
你要记住  你还是一名美国军官
Then when you are prepared to remember that you are still an officer
尽管你现在没穿着军装
in the United States Army, in spite of your civilian attire,
当兵的就要有当兵的样
and are ready to present that question in a military fashion,
这样我们才能谈的下去
then perhaps we could get somewhere with this discussion.
如果你派遣天龙特攻队去了巴格达
lf you have sent an Alpha Team into Baghdad for any reason whatsoever,
就已经违抗了国防部的命令
that is a direct violation of a DoD order.
既然你都这么说了
Well, and as much as you have this kind of knowledge,
还问我作甚
I can't help wondering why it is that you need to ask anything of me.
我就当你是承认了
I will take that as your confirmation, sir.
他们三小时后出发
They go mobile in three hours.
在铸币厂里将模板和十多亿美元
The plates and over a billion dollars
装在一辆拖车后面
will be loaded into the back of a semi at the mint.
然后行驶7.4公里到达这座桥
They're overland for exactly 4.6 miles before they reach the bridge.
这是我们的机会  但转瞬即逝
That's our window, and it closes fast.
一有任何风吹草动  他们都会开大火力
These guys will go weapons hot at the first whisper of trouble.
小白  你得进入酒店地下
Face, your point of entry is under the hotel.
酒店上面肯定挤满了外国记者和私人保镖
It'll be packed with foreign press and private security.
怪头  你带着计时器等在这条巷子里
B.A., you're in this alleyway on a stopwatch.
车起码要是双气缸引擎
Make sure the bike has V-tins or better.
我弄了辆比那强百倍的
I got something a whole lot better than that.
我干什么呀  头儿
What about me, boss man?
我有架小型直升机
I had a little helicopter here someplace.
能不能空翻  或是空中熄火
You got some barrel rolls? Some mid-air stalls?
我等不及下一次濒死体验了
I'm looking for my next near-death experience.
你这次是支援行动  上尉
Only air support this time, Captain,
下次会让你大干一场  我保证
but I'll get you in on the next one. I promise.
怪头  你六点半准时出发
B.A., I need you to pop that clutch at 0630.
我吗
Is that me?
我都忘了  我在伊拉克的下水道里  太谢谢了  头儿
Oh, no, l forgot. I'm in an lraqi sewer. Thanks, boss!
时间就是一切  小白
Timing is everything, Face.
关键要一击即中
This is all about the bull's-eyes.
谁说不是
Why not?
在拖车下面  你得把跟在后面的卡车干掉
From under the semi, you'll take out the truck directly behind you.
然后会有人冲着你过来  小白
Now, these guys are gonna be onto you, Face.
怪头  这时就该你上场了
B.A., that's your cue for throttle.
穿越前先看清两旁的路
Be sure to look both ways before crossing.
还有别忘了给车加满油
And have a nice full tank of gas.
车上会有重兵把守  怪头
You'll have multiple hostiles on board, B.A.
把他们统统解决掉
Escort them from the premises.
要是有人从后面偷袭  别担心  有我呢
If any stragglers sneak up behind, don't worry, l got your back.
抓住你了  小子
Gotcha, kid.
好样的
Attaboy.
听起来不错  但我们要怎么离开巴格达呢
That's all fine in theory, but I still don't see how we get out of Baghdad.
我心中有数
I do.
怪头  右转
B.A.! Hang a right!
好的  抓紧
All right! Hang on!
-小心  -低头
- Watch out! Watch out!   - Heads down!
干得漂亮  怪头
Oh! Nice one, B.A. !
小白  装上气囊
Face, get the airbags!
得保证一会儿不会脱落
Gotta make sure this thing stays locked for later!
完美
Beautiful!
一  二  三
One, two, three.
头儿  气囊是为了防撞击的吧
Hey, boss, airbags do deploy on impact, right?
怪头  到集装箱里去
B.A., get in the container.
注意后方
Contact, rear!
靠
Shit!
我就觉得这部分最不靠谱
See, this is the part of the plan l don't trust!
别担心  小白  绳子很牢
Don't worry, Face! The rope will hold!
我担心会被钉在集装箱上
If l was worried, l'd be nailing myself to the container right now!
抓住了  弟兄们
Hang on, boys!
老子来也  统统给我轰成渣吧
Bam! Come on! l smoked you!
你们看到下面的情况了没
You boys see that down there?
那傻蛋来干什么
Murdock? What is that fool doing here?
让我出去  我不是开玩笑
Don't lock me in here. l ain't playing with y'all!
头儿  你有没有在游戏厅玩过
Hey, boss, you ever play that game at the fun fair
用爪子抓玩具的游戏
where you try to pick up a stuffed animal with the claw?
这感觉太像啦
This is a lot like that.
就是这样
That's it!
你们锁上了是么
Did you lock this?
你们锁上了是么  你们竟然我把锁住了
You locked it, didn't you?
汉尼拔  快开门呀  伙计
Hannibal, open this door right now, man!
你是在把这车厢往哪儿挂吗
What the... Are you hooking this thing?
-是往直升机上挂吗  -挂好了
- You hooking this up to a helicopter?   - I got you.
到底他妈怎么回事  别这么疯狂
What the hell's going on?   You ain't that crazy!
别他妈告我现在我在天上  看我怎么弄死你们
Tell me we ain't flying! I'm gonna kill you, fool!
-头儿  那是博斯克吗  -快放我出去
- Boss, is that Bosco?  - Get me out of here!
-糟了  -快放我出去
- That's not good.  - Let me out of here!
这下糟了  他不高兴了
That's not good. He is not happy.
林奇特工  我临时从
Agent Lynch, I'm patching surveillance
将军账营中打给你
from the General's tent to you now.
长官  现在有架可倾斜旋翼的V22型飞机
Sir, l have an inbound V-22 tilt-rotor
从西北方向接近
on approach from the northwest.
是友非敌  奉将军之命在此降落
Identified friendly. Landing under the General's orders.
是天龙特攻队撤退至此  不是敌人
Alpha Delta Alpha, stand down. Checked, friendly.
喀布尔  阿富汗
是我们的人  在临时着陆区的D区
Those are our boys. D-block perimeter around LZ
携带重要物品降落
for essential cargo touchdown.
老罗  大获全胜
Russ, we are in the net.
收到  我五分钟后到
Copy that. l will be there in five.
用一大瓶尊尼获加蓝方为你们接风
I've got a big bottle of Blue Label waiting.
一瓶哪够  最起码一箱才行  吝啬鬼
A bottle? Make it a case, Scrooge.
一会儿见
See you in a few.
谁去放他出来
Who's gonna let him out?
-你去  -你去
- You!  - You!
你们都小心着点  等我出去搞死你们
What you don't realize is, now l gotta kill all of y'all!
丫的搞死你们  先灭汉尼拔  然后是默多克
I'll kill all of y'all! Hannibal first, then Murdock!
-头儿  -最后是小白
- Boss man.  - I'm gonna save Face for last!
-让我试试  -去吧
- Let me try something.  - Go for it.
真是诡异  我觉得他比那任务还可怕
ls it weird that I'm more scared now than what we just did?
博斯克  我是默多克
Bosco, it's Murdock.
默多克  快开门
Murdock, open this door!
乖  我给你做你爱吃的椰奶咖喱橄榄沙司哟
I'll make you some of that coconut-curry tapenade that you love.
这招估计管用
That might work.
有吐司吗
With toast points?
当然有吐司  不然
Hell, yeah, with toast points. What, you're gonna have that
要抹在土豆饼上吃吗
with plain old chips?
-你玩儿我  -猛虎出栅喽
- Damn! You tricked me.  - There he is.
-出来喽  -我讨厌这样
- There he is!  - I hate that!
-得了  -离我远点  伙计
- Come on!  - Get away from me, man!
要不是寡不敌众我真想揍扁你们
The only reason l don't kick y'all asses is 'cause you all outrank me.
你搞明白点  我讨厌在天上飞
You should know better! You know l hate flying!
我满身是汗  臭气熏天
I'm wet! I stink!
我还一毛钱都花不了
And l can't spend none of that money!
-用钱买不来幸福  -去你丫的
- Money can't buy happiness.  - Damn, man!
默多克  今晚你来做饭  穿上你的小花围裙
Hey, Murdock, you cooking tonight. You better get your apron on.
我就爱计划圆满的那一刻
I love it when a plan comes together.
-汉尼拔  谁在里面  -是将军吗
- Hannibal, who was that?  - General?
-里面是将军吗  -老罗
- ls that the General?  - Russ.
-到这儿来  -将军
- Get there. Get in there.  -  General!
-老罗  -将军
- Russ!  - General!
将军
General!
天哪
Jesus Christ.
帕克
Pike.
注意后方
Contact rear!
过去
Get in there!
快过去
Get there, get there!
经过商议  我们决定将你
After conferring, we've decided to demote you
降级到中尉
to the rank of First Lieutenant.
索萨中尉  虽不是你的过失
Lieutenant Sosa, it's nothing personal,
但你却没能弄回模板
but you lost those plates.
那便是你的责任
Those were your responsibility.
你就庆幸吧
Consider yourself lucky.
其他人要为此去蹲监狱
Others are going to prison over this.
您好  麦克雷迪检察官
Good day, Director McCready.
中尉  你可以走了
Lieutenant, you're dismissed.
史密斯上校  本庭无法证实
Colonel Smith, this court has been unable to recover
你执行的那项任务是遵从
any direct order from General Morrison for you to conduct the mission
莫里森将军的命令
for which you're being tried.
法官大人  这是秘密行动
Your Honor, this was a covert operation
并无官方命令
and no official orders were given.
但唯一能证明此项行动合法性的人
So the one individual who can verify
已经去世了  对吧  上校
the legitimacy of this operation is deceased. Is that correct, Colonel?
不对  法官大人  不是去世
No, Your Honor, not deceased.
罗素・莫里森将军
美国陆军
莫里森将军是被谋杀的
General Morrison was murdered.
上校  像你们这种不守军规的人
Colonel, I've been around a long time.
我见的多了
I've seen units like yours. They're outlaws.
就是你们这种人
Units like that pose a direct threat
对我军的军威军纪造成了巨大威胁
to the fabric and fundamentals of our military.
法官大人  为何"黑森林"没有被问责
Your Honors, why hasn't Black Forest been brought to trial?
黑森林及其成员不在我们的管辖范围内
Black Forest and its personnel are not subject to military jurisdiction.
你的计划呢  头儿
Where's the plan, boss? Where is it?
逃跑计划呢  我没看到呢
Where's the escape hatch? Because l don't see it.
-这项任务还没结束  中尉  -什么任务
- This mission isn't over, Lieutenant.  - What mission?
找到帕克和模板  就能洗清罪名
I clear our names. We find Pike and the plates.
不惜一切代价
No matter what.
法官大人  这些人只是依令办事
Your Honors, these men were acting under my command.
所有处罚都应由我一人承担
Any judgment should be levied against me, and me alone.
并非如此  长官
Absolutely not, sir.
我们都是自愿参与此行动
We were all participating in this operation willingly.
我不赞成个人顶责
I don't wanna be tried separately.
我也拒绝个人顶责  长官
I refuse to be tried separately, sir.
根据军事审判统一法典
In accordance with the Uniform Code of Military Justice,
本庭判决A小队  即天龙特攻队
this court is rendering guilty verdicts
所有成员罪名成立
for each member of this Alpha Unit, or A-Team,
并委托监狱对你们分开进行最严密监禁
and mandating incarceration in separate maximum-security facilities
在未来十年内
for a period of up to 10 years.
撤销你们的军衔
You're all hereby stripped of formal rank
并开除军籍  永不录用
and dishonorably discharged.
简直是放屁
This is bullshit, man.
现在休庭
This session is adjourned.
可耻
Disgraceful.
-别碰我  -上尉  退下
- Do not touch me, okay?  - Captain, stand down.
安静
Order! Order!
绝对的诬陷
Absolute disgrace!
你高兴了吧  查瑞莎
You happy? Are you happy, Charissa?
上校  管好你的人
Colonel, control your men!
-把你的手拿开  -这是诬陷
- Get your hands off me!  - This is a disgrace!
六个月后
军 事 监 狱
科罗拉多
卡森要塞
好久不见  林奇先生
Well, hello, Mr. Lynch. Long time.
在这么多摄像头下
You look very relaxed, Lynch.
你还能这样放松
A lot of cameras in here.
确实挺多
Yeah, there are.
但现在它们都有些技术故障
Yeah, well, they seem to be having some technical issues at the moment.
看来录像里是找不到我了
May not show up till playback.
汉尼拔  能这么称呼你吗
Hannibal. Can l call you Hannibal?
不能再叫你上校了
I can't call you Colonel anymore.
我等了
Six months.
你六个月  等着你把这儿炸飞
Been waiting for you to bust out of here
再召回那帮小兄弟
and round up the rest of the Backstreet Boys
带我去找模板
and lead me to those plates.
但六个月却毫无音讯
Six months and not a peep.
所有人都以为你们是和帕克一伙儿的
Everybody thought you and your team were working with Pike.
除了你
Mmm. Everybody except you.
帕克谋杀了莫里森  设计陷害我们  偷走了模板
Pike murdered Morrison. Set me and my boys up and stole those plates.
我知道他在哪儿
And I know where he is.
没人知道他在哪儿
Nobody knows where he is.
这有一张他被拍到的照片
It's a single image of him.
一个月前在欧洲的某处
Taken about a month ago, somewhere in Europe.
大概是监控摄像头的抓拍
We think it's a grab from a CCTV camera.
是德国的法兰克福
Frankfurt, Germany.
你怎么知道
How did you get that in here?
我需要的只是时间  林奇
Time, Lynch.
1分钟我就能做到这样
Give me a minute and I'm good.
给1小时我会更出色
If I've got an hour, I'm great.
要是给我半年时间  我就无敌了
You give me six months, I'm unbeatable.
帕克我认识
I know Pike.
那个阿拉伯人是谁
Who's the Arab?
不知道
We don't know.
我们觉得他是"深黑"  整个事件的幕后黑手
We think he's the deep, dark, hidden hand in this whole thing.
或是经纪人  或是买主
Maybe a broker, maybe a buyer.
林奇  我们有共同的敌人  而你却只有一个选择
Lynch, we have common enemies and you have limited choices.
我的队伍是你夺回模板的最好选择
My team is still your best shot at getting those plates back.
这我得想一想
I wouldn't be so sure.
那你干吗大老远跑到这儿来
Then why did you make the long drive out here?
你和中情局的伙计们正等着你的决定
You and your boys at Langley want your own private printing press.
行不行就取决于你的爱国心了
That's about as deep as your patriotism goes.
那你需要我如何协助
So, what would you need from me?
我答应过队员们会为他们洗清罪名
I swore to my team that I would clear our names.
你们都该明白名誉的重要性
You of all people must understand the value of a name.
听着
Now, listen.
我要求复职与洗清罪名
I want full reinstatement and clean records
我和我的队员们
for myself and my team.
我无法把你弄出去
I can't get you out of here.
至少合法的途径上不行
Not legally, at least.
这是中情局的拿手菜
This is something the boys at Langley do very, very well.
浸5毫升河豚毒素的古巴雪茄
剂量一定要准确
Make sure the dosage is right.
准确的意思就是毫厘不差
And when I say right, I mean perfect.
我的幸福鸟呀她还没来到
Don't seem like happiness will come along
古巴货 可惜了
Cuban. What a shame.
大家都往我床上丢石块
Everybody's throwing rocks in my bed
生活停滞不前
Just can't seem to get ahead in life
火葬室
为啥我就搞不定
Ooh, nothing I do ever turn out right
"战神"  约翰・史密斯  被捕后死于心脏病
为啥没人来帮帮我
Won't somebody help me, please?
我已寂寞很久了
'Cause I've been lonely for so long
我的幸福鸟呀她还没来到
Don't seem like happiness will come along
我已寂寞
I've been lonely...
休想在我的
You are not permitted
道场撒野
in my dojo!
看来  撒旦显灵了
So, Satan walks into this bar...
等等  这都什么  泳池
Wait a minute. What's this, a lap pool?
蒸汽房
A dry steam room?
是啊  还要用很久呢
Yeah, it'll go a long way with the boys.
你到底怎么弄来的
How in the hell do you pull this off?
这不在于和谁关系好  鲍勃  而在于你们关系有多好
It's not who you know, Bob, it's how you know them.
联邦营地监狱
彭萨科拉
弗罗里达
你儿子从阿富汗回来了吗
Oh! Did your boy get back from Afghanistan?
对  多亏回来了  我和孩他妈都高兴的不得了
Yeah. Thanks for getting him home. His mother and l are real grateful.
上尉
Captain.
你忘东西在我床上了
You left something on the bed.
-你应该藏起来  -藏起来多浪费
- Could have hid those.  - Why would I want to do that?
太销魂了  八点见
Drive me crazy. I'll see you at 8:00.
-你还要建什么  -泳池和蒸汽房已经有了
-And now you want to build...  -A lap pool and a dry steam.
对了  还要一个日光浴场所
Overlooking a sundeck.
谢谢你的靴子
Hey, LT, thanks for the boots.
客气啥  我的荣幸  宝贝儿
Ah! Come on. It's my pleasure, baby!
漂亮
Beautiful.
听着  我知道这对身体有好处
Listen, now l know this is good for the body,
但怎样保护脸不被晒伤
but how do you protect the face?
小子  你的脸再黑也很帅
You don't mess with it, kid.
呵呵
Gotcha.
-谢谢请我做日光浴  -不客气
- Thanks for the tan. - You got it.
史密斯越狱了  中尉
Smith has escaped, Lieutenant.
我去抓他回来
Let me go after him.
史密斯他们和布拉德・帕克的黑森林勾结
Smith and his team were working with Brock Pike and Black Forest.
找到他们就能找回模板  长官
I can get those plates back for you, sir.
相信我
You know I can.
哼哼哈嘿
Holla what? Holla who?
哼哼哈
Holla me.
放我出去
Hey! Let me out! Hey, hey! Hey!
我当时就看到他站在那儿  我都傻了  我还以为是鬼
I see him standing there, and I was like, "What?"
他全身乌黑  等我醒来   脸上还很麻木
And then it turned black and I woke up, and my face was numb,
我就
and l just...
你就把他的脚印都用拖把擦了
And you mopped up the footprints that led out,
连你的实验大褂丢了也没发觉
ignored the fact that your lab coat,
还有通行证  车钥匙和你的车
pass card, car keys and car were missing.
胖得好像吞了史密斯在肚中
Looks like he ate Smith.
吉伯特  你或者蓄意
Gilbert, you've either deliberately
与一名联邦罪犯策划越狱
aided and abetted a federal fugitive's escape,
或者就是你笨得可以
or you're the single dumbest human being I've ever come into contact with.
-你闻到了吗   -啥也别说
- You smell that?   - Don't talk about it.
你想知道为啥我要倾着身子吗
Would you like to know which way I'm leaning?
前锋的职业病
Forward.
每小时给这家伙做一次尿检
I would test this man's urine, on the hour.
距离我的假释听证会就差一周啊
I was a week away from my parole hearing.
你晒得还真黑啊
You are really tan.
跟你说过了这任务还没完
Told you the mission wasn't over.
我要重组天龙特攻队
I'm putting the team back together.
天龙特攻队不能没有你  小白
I need you, Face. I can't do this without you.
狱长  为啥有人可以不经你同意去探望史密斯
Warden, how did Smith arrange a personal visit without your consent
你也没签字通过呀  这咋就发生了
or your signature? How does that happen?
这该死的家伙怎么办到的
How the hell did this guy do that?
封锁起来  谁都不许进去
Seal that up, nobody goes in there.
没有探监那天的登记记录
Log-in pages from the day in question have been removed.
-意料之中  -被撕掉了
- Why does that not surprise me?  - Torn out.
雪茄藏在那本书的书脊里
The cigar was in the spine of that book.
-真精密  这书不错  -不错
- Subtle. It's a good book.  - Right.
这是全方位监视犯人的摄像录像
This is surveillance from all around the prison, right?
而屏幕上出现的扭曲是信号干扰
What you're watching is a signal jammer.
每当他路过这些探头时
Every time he walks through one of these things,
一拍到他的摄像头都会受到信号干扰
we get massive interference. He waltzes in here and waltzes out.
没人知道他是谁
Nobody knows who he is.
天呀
God.
哦  这就是那根帮助史密斯上校越狱的雪茄
Yes. The cigar that Colonel Smith broke out of prison with.
-知道比这更不可思议的是什么吗   -是什么
- Yeah. Wanna hear the crazy part?  - Yes.
实验检测到这里面含有足以致命剂量的河豚毒素
Lab reports show lethal amounts of, wait for it, tetrodotoxin.
河豚毒素   那是什么
Tetrodotoxin? What is that?
-可以濒死的药物  -能让人成为睡美人的玩意
-The near-death drug. -Yes, that sleeping beauty thing.
你知道什么人会用这玩意吗
Yeah. And you know who likes to use that, right?
-谁  -名字都叫林某某的那些人
-Who? -Our friends at Langley.
这是他们的拿手好戏
It's one of their favorites.
你觉得是中情局的人来找的史密斯吗
Come on, do you really think that the CIA came to the prison to visit Smith?
虽然有些离谱  但我觉得是中情局帮他越狱的
This sounds kind of crazy, but l think the CIA broke him out.
谁帮的忙
Who put us on?
就是在巴格达的那个人  中情局的林奇
The same guy that put us on in Baghdad. Lynch, CIA.
为了什么  洗清罪名吗  还是复职
What are we talking about? Clean records? Reinstatements?
都是
All of the above.
那帕克呢  还有模板
What about Pike and the plates?
要他们付出代价
Payback.
他们在交换什么  在做什么
What are they exchanging?  What is that?
他就是这样进来的吗
Is that how he got this in here?
找找两张图中的不图之处
One of these things is not like the other.
这种游戏我可不在行
I suck at these games.
模板从哪座楼里带出来的  模板上倒映的是什么
Where's this plate from? What is that plate?
字母F  德国法兰克福
It's an "F." Frankfurt, Germany.
哦  德国法兰克福
Oh, Frankfurt, Germany.
史密斯在向我们暗示什么  这不会是巧合
Smith is talking to us. This is not accidental.
这家伙总是胸有成竹
With this guy, there's a plan and two to back it up.
你不是指什么因果报应吧
l take it you didn't get religion inside.
不  是复仇
No. l got revenge.
很好
Good.
我认识几个人  刚好也有这念头
I know a couple of guys that'll feel the exact same way.
正合我意
I'm counting on it.
塔霍湖
加拿大
索伯监狱转监车
《宽容与怜悯  救赎之路》
紧急状况
马上出来
紧急状况  马上出来
Emergency exit now.
汉尼拔
Hannibal.
紧急出口
拜库斯  别跑
Baracus, don't do it!
他去哪儿  他要干嘛
Where he going? What's he doing, man?
拜库斯  真他妈见鬼
Baracus! God damn it!
我是索萨
Sosa.
中尉  派克也越狱了
Lieutenant, Peck's already gone.
什么
What?
还剩拜库斯和默多克了  着手处理这件事  中尉
Baracus and Murdock are left. Handle it, Lieutenant.
好的
Right. Okay.
我不想再出这种丢脸的事了
I don't want to be embarrassed like this again. Do you?
好  别  别   我们马上就开始部署人员进行抓捕
Okay. No, no, no, no. We're gonna catch and deploy from here.
派克越狱了
Peck escaped.
-靠  你觉得与史密斯有关吗  -显然啊
-Oh, hell. You think Smith is involved?  -Definitely.
立刻准备他们的照片  任何可以立马识别出他们的
Get graphics on him and Smith. Anything that'll ID them instantly.
默多克被关在曼海姆精神病医院
I know they got Murdock in a psych ward in Mannheim.
怪头那家伙又他妈的在哪儿
Right. Okay. Where the hell is B.A. Baracus?
你怎么知道那个门
How did you know that once that door was extracted
-掉下来后能支撑他的体重  -我想嘛
- that it would take his weight?  - l just did. He's...
-他大概有102 104公斤吧  -104公斤
- You know, he's what, 225, 230 pounds?  - 230. Yeah.
你记得我们七年前在委内瑞拉的那次任务吗
Remember the gag we did in Venezuela seven years ago?
委内瑞拉  记得
Venezuela. Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
但那人个子很小
But that was a midget.
我考虑到了
Yeah, I wouldn't go for that.
-嘿  大块头  他来了  -回来了
- Hey, big guy. There he is.  - Yeah! He's back.
-回来真好  -得劲呀
- Yeah, it's good to be back.  - Come on.
-回来真好  伙计  -好伙计
- It's good to be back.  - My man.
-见到你真高兴  兄弟  -我们也是
- It's good to see you, bud.  - You, too, bro. You, too.
-谢谢  -你气色不错
- Thanks.  - You look well.
再见到你们真高兴
It's good to see you guys.
-怎么  -你的莫霍克发型呢
- What?  - Where's the Mohawk?
怎么  不喜欢我的新发型吗
What, you don't like my new do, man?
啥  不是给你准备推子推头了吗  我以为
Do I like it? Well, we got you the clippers. I thought...
我这不是用了嘛
Yeah, I used them.
怎么了  大块头
Hey. What's up, big guy?
跟我们讲讲
Come on, you can speak to us.
伙计们
Guys...
我不能再杀人了
I can't kill anybody.
-什么意思  -我发过誓
- What do you mean?  - I've taken a vow.
-什么誓  -远离暴力
- Vow?  - Of non-violence.
我仍会跟你们合作
I'll still do anything for you guys, you know that.
但我不会杀人
But I just can't kill, man.
虽然旧习难改
Old habits may die hard,
但终将改过
but they still gotta die.
小时候大家都说
When l was a kid, all you heard in the hood was,
博斯克是个大坏蛋  嗜杀如狂
"Bosco's a badass, out collecting scalps."
所以我留莫霍克头
That's where the Mohawk came from.
于是我一直在战斗
Was always at war.
这就是战士的宿命
And that's what warriors are for.
汉尼拔  伙计  我不想要这种生活
Hannibal, man. I don't miss that life.
我会帮忙把默多克弄出来  扭转我们的的不公待遇
I'll help you get Murdock, and right that wrong,
-但不能杀人  -帕克也不杀吗
- but I can't kill.  - Even Pike?
即使杀掉他能洗清你的罪名
Even if killing him would clear your name?
我现在只想对得起自己的良心
My conscience is the only thing l need clear.
那么  那个小疯子大蠢蛋在哪儿
Now, where's that crazy-ass fool?
情感转移
Transference.
情感康复
Healing feelings.
不能把感情全堆在心里
You can't warehouse these things, you know?
你只有发泄出来才会有所好转
You have to express to progress.
要为你的情感大厦添砖加瓦
We gotta empower your emotional tower
你要珍惜自己也要学会接受别人的爱
and send out a wavelength of self-love and acceptance.
谢谢
Thank you.
陆军精神病医院
德国曼海姆
就绪
Clear.
好像不起啥作用  这没法展开相应的治疗呀
He seems completely impervious to it. It's impossible to develop a base reading.
加大电压了吗
Have you increased the voltage?
每回都加
Every single session, yes.
-情感康复  宝贝  -结果呢
- Healing feelings, baby.  - And?
就这点威力吗  来吧
Is that all you got? Here we go.
就绪
Clear.
我觉得好像感觉到了什么
Yeah, I think I might have felt something there.
我不会入睡的
Oh, no, I won't sleep.
小霍华德
Howard Little.
安娜贝拉・史密斯寄给你的包裹
You have a package here from an Annabelle Smith.
我不认识这人
I don't know any Annabelle Smith.
你认识的  豪伊
Sure you do, Howie.
你肯定认识呀   安娜贝拉
Sure you do, baby. Annabelle.
还记得岘港市的那个护士不   红头发  双腿残疾的那姑娘
Remember the nurse from Da Nang? The redhead, double amputee?
她有架专业级的悬挂式滑翔机  想起没
Professional hang glider? Yes!
伙计们
Guys.
安娜贝拉
Annabelle.
安娜贝拉   超越了自我  看看
Annabelle. You have outdone yourself. Look at this.
-太真实啦  -真美
- It's so real.  - Beauty.
3D电影
A movie in three dimensions.
准备战斗  我的士兵
Stand-to, soldier.
-敌军在逼近西部战线  -老天呀
- Jerries advancing on the western front.  - Good heavens.
派你去执行一项秘密任务
Got a secret mission for you.
把这些分发给大伙
Take these and distribute them amongst the men.
-遵命  长官  - 不要辜负女王殿下
-Yes, sir. -Don't fail the Queen.
-一定完成任务  -好样的
- No, sir.  - Great.
遵命
Yes, sir.
看电影  看电影
Movie, movie, movie...
我将授爵于你
l knight you.
你得把头低下  站起来重做
Sir, you have to put your head down. Stand up and do it again.
电影
Movie, movie...
现在让我们为女王殿下放声歌唱   听我指挥   先别坐下
Now let's sing to the Queen.  When l ask you... Not yet.
-看电影  看电影  -看电影  看电影
- Movie, movie...  - Movie, movie...
你们拿到眼镜了
You get glasses! You get glasses!
球来了
Ball!
跪下的时候得低下头
When you kneel, you put your head down straightaway.
抬头盯着我看是不尊重的  明白吗
Looking me in the eye is disrespectful. Do you understand?
看电影
Movie, movie...
你正盯着我看  不对
You're looking me in the eye now. That's wrong.
看电影
Movie, movie, movie...
水族先生  你好
Aquaman? Hello.
你们拿到眼镜了
You get glasses! You get glasses!
起立  3D先生  好好享受电影的乐趣吧
Rise, Sir 3D, and enjoy your motion picture.
-看电影  -看电影
-Movie! Movie! -Movie! Movie!
伙计  我能离开两小时不
Boy, could l use two hours of not this.
准备好镇静剂  再给这帮疯子要点比萨饼
Pass out the sedatives and order some pizzas for these freaks.
-看电影  -看电影
-Movie, movie... -Movie, movie...
看电影
Movie...
靠
Shit.
有什么需要帮忙吗
Excuse me, can l help you with something?
有  我们找默多克上尉  他在哪儿
Yes. Captain Murdock, where is he?
-那边的房间里  -谢谢
- Right through there.  - Thank you.
霹雳教头
El diablo.
电影
行了  都坐下
Okay. Settle down.
看电影不许说话
No talking during the movie.
前面坐下
Down in front!
看呀  伙计  这是立体的
Look, it's 3D, man!
我看3D的片子有点晕
I'm sick of 3D.
默多克上尉
Captain Murdock.
记得我吗  在巴格达见过的
You remember me from Baghdad?
简直是无用功  这是个傻子
Okay, this is pointless. This guy is fried.
所以他才呆在这儿
Yeah, there's a reason why he's in here.
除他以外的所有天龙队员都已越狱
And his entire team has escaped, except him.
电影
Movie!
注意观察周围  不要让别人靠近他
Take a look around anyway. Let's make sure he's alone.
遵命  女士
Yes, ma'am.
更大的逃亡  恶搞电影《大逃亡》(1963)
亲爱滴上尉  您的战车正侯驾
Oh, Captain, your chariot awaits.
抱歉小的们  先走一步  电影就这么没啦
Sorry, boys, gotta run! Can't finish the movie.
得让我看到结尾吧
Do let me know how it ends.
查瑞莎  你藏哪儿呢  别气皱你那漂亮脸蛋儿  宝贝
Charissa, where are you hiding? Stay beautiful, baby.
你们应该去看看3D电影中子弹横飞的画面
You guys should see these bullets in 3D!
追上那车
Get the truck!
他们在朝我们射击
She's actually shooting at us.
子弹还是3D的呢
You guys should see these bullets in 3D!
-把头收回来  -像真的被枪打一样耶
- Murdock, get in here!  - It's like we're actually being shot at!
你再这样真的会吃枪子  疯子大蠢蛋
You are getting shot at, you crazy-ass fool!
-马上停车  -撞飞它
- Stop right there!  - Ram it.
我说停下
Hey! I said halt!
爽  抱歉啦伙计
Damn! Sorry, dude.
他们好像朝飞机跑道去了
lt looks like they're headed for the tarmac.
快出发
Let's go, let's go, let's go.
-先生们  -该死  是汉尼拔・史密斯
- Gentlemen.  - Holy shit, that's Hannibal Smith.
你们有谁是持枪逃跑的联邦逃犯吗
Are any of you armed and/or wanted federal fugitives?
-没有  -但我们都是
- No.  - Well, we're both.
-那么  -我不喜欢这个主意
- Which means...  - This is a bad idea.
这是个坏点子
This is a bad idea.
别这么孩子气  上飞机去  像个大人一样
Stop being a baby. You're a grown-ass man. Get on the plane.
-你要劫机吗  -所以我才加入陆军
- You're taking the plane?  - And that's why I joined the Army.
男人点儿  快进去  我们要胜利大逃亡了
We gotta finish the escape. Man up and get in there.
你们是最聪明最顶尖的人才  非常感谢  你们可以走了
The best and brightest. Appreciate it, boys. That'll be all.
钥匙咧  我要钥匙
Who's got the keys? l just need your keys.
-什么狗屁钥匙  -开飞机难道不要钥匙的吗
- What you talking about keys?  - You don't need no keys for no plane.
-我真的需要钥匙  -干毛用  真是馊主意
- I do need keys.  - For what? This is a bad idea.
我们刚把这疯子从精神病院弄出来
We just broke this guy out of a psych ward.
汉尼拔  还是用刚才那些真的飞行员比较靠谱
Hannibal, you let the real pilots go.
-怪头  放心  没问题的  -吃一颗
- B.A., relax. You're gonna be fine.  - Take one of these.
这是啥  要把我弄晕吗  最好是把我弄晕
What is this? Will it knock me out? It better knock me out,
不然晕的就是你
'cause if it don't, I'm gonna knock you out.
博斯克  这些按钮让我很迷茫
Bosco, the buttons are confusing me.
-闭嘴  默多克   -拜托了  默多克  快走
- Shut up, Murdock.  - Come on, Murdock. Let's go.
让我坐这破飞机  算了吧  我还不如去自首
You gonna fly this plane? Forget it. I'll turn myself in.
-这是干啥用的  -快点
- What does this do?  - Come on.
-快点  默多克  -运气真好
- Come on, Murdock.  - I got lucky.
扶好了  小的们
Hang on, boys.
停
Stop. Stop, stop, stop.
小白  你女朋友耶
Face, your girlfriend is back.
-立刻倒车  -我操他妈的
- Reverse now.  - Son of a bitch!
快点倒车
Move your ass now.
C-1 30型运输机和梅赛德斯-奔驰的巅峰对决
The C-1 30 versus the Mercedes-Benz.
快起飞  默多克
Lift us off, Murdock.
-再快点   -快点
- How about faster?  - Faster!
我尽力  全速行进了
I'm trying. l got it pinned!
上帝呀
Oh, my God!
接飞行控制中心
Get us to flight control.
女士们  先生们  稍后飞机会稍有颠簸
Ladies and gentlemen, we are expecting slight turbulence.
请在座位上不要离开直到机长
Please remain in your seats until the captain has turned off
解除警报
the "Fasten Seatbelt" sign.
孩子们别担心  小小颠簸不足恐惧
Don't worry, boys! Turbulence has never brought down a plane!
他妈的那是什么
What the hell is that?
我们被亚音速无人机和导弹锁定了
But we got inbound subsonic UAVs with missile lock!
它们简直就是灰机的天敌
And they bring down planes all the time!
他们来了  反导弹装置发射
Okay, they're coming in. Launching countermeasures!
看到没  命悬一线刺激吧
Did you see that? That's my diversion!
它们被我灭了
They die on this version.
坚持住  我们转过去
Hang on! Hang on! Hold on! We're going over.
默多克  你他妈的发什么疯
Murdock, what the hell are you doing?
想念墨西哥的时候了吗
You boys remember Mexico?
飞机上的女士们和先生们
Ladies and gentlemen, from the flight deck,
如果你稍微往右边看一下的话  就会发现
if you look out of the right-hand side of the aircraft, you'll notice
我们的右边机翼已经着火
that your right wing is on fire.
-请回复  -导弹锁定待命  长官
- Tango reacquired.   - Missile lock pending, sir.
查瑞莎・索萨中尉  那些人是国防部罪案调查处的重犯
Lieutenant Charissa Sosa, DClS. Major,
不要击落那架飞机
do not shoot that aircraft down.
紧急出动战斗机  逼迫他们降落
Scramble fighters and force them to land.
机上有联邦逃犯
There are federal fugitives on that plane.
他们还偷窃了美军财物
They've also stolen property from the U.S. Army.
比利  快把输出扫描从屏幕上去掉
Billy, Billy, l need you to get the nose-cam view up here on my monitor now.
移上去了  长官  好了
It's up, sir. Here it is.
导弹已发射
Missile away, sir.
击中  成功拦截和摧毁海格力斯号
We have shoot-down. Hercules has been intercepted and destroyed.
我很抱歉  中尉
Sorry, Lieutenant. I'm sorry.
-不是吧   -长官  毕福德号坦克上有降落伞
- l don't believe it.  - We have chute deployment on the Buford.
什么
What?
立刻让那些无人机停下来
l want these drones taken offline right now!
-离这儿十万八千里呢  -不管是谁在操控
- They're 3,000 miles away.  - Whoever is running those drones.
给我拨专线电话  不管是谁
Get me a direct line to whoever is running those drones.
快让那些无机停下来  我该遭批斗了
We gotta get these drones to stand down or I'm gonna be on bitch duty.
我们要活捉那些人
I need to get those men alive!
大家还好吗
Everybody okay?
他们会觉得我们已经挂了吗
What are the chances they think we're dead?
可能性不大
Not great.
-我们不在飞机上了吧  -我们真不在那架飞机上了
- Tell me we ain't still on that plane.  - We ain't on that plane.
汉尼拔
Hannibal!
只要在两万英尺以下  就死不了吧
If we're under 20,000 feet, we can still breathe, right?
什么两万英尺
What are you talking about, 20,000 feet?
-咱们启动旧火力系统吧  -见鬼
- Let's fire up the old weapons system.  - What the hell, man?
博斯克  这儿闷死了  我要开个窗
Hey, Bosco, a little stuffy. I'm gonna pop a window!
奶奶滴  看谁有能耐  比比吧
What you got, bitches? What you got?
小白  也让我来耍耍  快点嘛
Let me have a turn, Face! Come on!
-我们怎么会呆在一个坠落的坦克里  -因为飞机爆炸了
- Why are we in a falling tank?  - Because the plane exploded!
什么  啥时候
What... What? When?
就刚才
Recently!
-被收割者击落了  -什么收割者
- The Reapers shot it down!  - What Reapers?
就是那些现在还穷追不舍的家伙
The same ones that are still trying to kill us!
-汉尼拔  都怪你  -严格来讲  我们没在飞了嘛
- l blame you, Hannibal!  - Technically, we're not flying.
废话  我们是在坠落  混蛋
I know! Because we're falling, fool!
额滴神啊
Oh, Jesus!
2号无人机坠落  我们损失了一架无人机
UAV-2 has splashed down. We just lost one of the drones.
汉尼拔  这下我们惨了
Hannibal, we're in trouble!
伙计们绷紧了
Brace yourselves!
爽翻天了
Awesome!
小白  你操纵主炮
Face, get on to the main gun!
离这八百米的地方有个湖
There's a lake a half-mile away from this position.
-我操他妈的朝谁开火啊  -相信我
- What the hell am l trying to hit?  - Trust me!
-把机枪转到82度  -开火
- Rotate the turret 82 degrees.  - Fire in the hole!
开火
Fire!
他们是想再射落一架无人机吗
Are they trying to shoot down that other drone?
不  他们是在驾驶坦克
No. They're trying to fly that tank.
-坦克飞起来咯  -坦克飞不起来  傻逼
- He's flying the tank!  - You can't fly a tank, fool!
-转到16度  开火  -收到
- Rotate 16 degrees!  - Got it!
开火
Fire!
再转到34度
Rotate 34 degrees now!
-汉尼拔  -等下
- Hannibal...  - Wait...
开火
Fire!
-控制中心  我们失去了无人机  -确定击中了吗
- Control, we have lost...  - Is that a confirmed hit?
右转正前方  待命
Bring turret full-front and wait!
默多克  关闭舱门
Murdock! Close the hatch!
收到  这样能行不
Hatch, okay! Did that work? Did that work?
-头儿  -加把劲呀
- Boss!  - Come on, baby.
-加把劲  -关好舱口没
- Come on.  - Hatch control?
我还不想这么早死
I'm too young to die!
头儿  现在都不用瞄准了
Boss! I'm aiming at nothing!
加把劲
Come on.
-先生们  我很荣幸  -加把劲  宝贝儿
- It's been an honor, gentlemen.  - Come on, baby.
最后一次飞行终生难忘啊  上校
The greatest ride is the last ride, Colonel!
-全力开火  -来吧  宝贝
- Fire everything!  - Come on, baby!
我的驾驶技术如何
-上帝保佑呀  上帝显灵吧  -加把劲
- Get right with God, y'all! This is it!   - Come on!
这对鱼类不公平
It's not fair to the fish!
你作弊
You're cheating!
真唠叨
You with your nagging...
把鱼都吓跑了
...you're chasing them away!
中情局国外办事处
德国  法兰克福
好了  辛勤的小蜜蜂
All right. Busy bees, busy bees.
把外套脱了吧  太他妈热了
Guys, you can take your coats off. Hot as hell in here.
热得跟蒸桑拿一样
I'm sweating like a whore in church.
-长官  -什么事
- Sir.  - Yeah?
史密斯一伙人在德国曼海姆劫了一架C1 30运输机
Smith and his team were engaged in a C-1 30 over Mannheim, Germany,
还击落了两架无人机
by two Reaper drones.
不知道是不是数据加密出了故障
I'm not sure if it's an encryption glitch,
但报告里说是被一辆坦克击落
but it says that they were shot down in a tank.
北美空防司令部想掩盖为失踪  但麻烦的是我们
NORAD's calling it an X-out, but there is a conflicting report.
我就知道
I'm sure there is.
一名德国老妇说她看到一辆坦克
I've got a German Hausfrau who says she saw a tank
从沃格斯坦湖里驶出来  坦克里有个人长得很像默多克
drive up and out of Lake Wolgastsee with a guy resembling Murdock...
打扰一下  柏林怎么走
Excuse me, which way to Berlin?
-问她柏林去怎么走  -这不可能
- ...asking for directions to Berlin.  - That's impossible.
史密斯一周内都死了两次了
Well, this will be the second time Smith has died this week.
对他们来说还有什么不可能的呢
ls that possible?
美国驻欧洲指挥部
德国  斯图加特
-有什么消息  -看看这个
- What have you got for me?  - Look at this.
我们对史密斯的访客图像进行了还原
We just got the unscrambled composite of Smith's visitor in prison,
但没有查到该人身份
but with no lD on the subject yet.
你好  帅哥
Hello, handsome.
等下  我以前见过他
Wait, I've seen this person before.
我认识这人
l know this guy.
巴格达
Baghdad.
给我洗张清晰的出来  我们开始行动
Get me a clean patch to Langley. We're going fishing.
我都没听说过
I barely even heard about it.
我零碎地听说了些  但这些怎么跟我们扯上了关系
I mean, I heard bits and pieces of it, but how much of that was us?
-我已经  -我在说话呢
- So, l have a...  - l was talking.
-不会和我们牵扯上的  -别说了好吗
- It's never us.  - Can you stop?
国防部的索萨中尉打来电话
l have a DoD hardline from Lieutenant Sosa.
她找林奇特工
She's looking for Agent Lynch.
林奇特工没空  一直没空
He's not available, ever.
巴格达的林奇特工
Agent Lynch, from Baghdad?
在莫里森将军的帐篷那次
General Morrison's tent?
出去
Out.
为什么雇她
Why do we have her?
因为她超有个性
She's got a fantastic personality. That's why.
请问哪位
With whom am l speaking?
我是索萨上  中尉  你是林奇特工吗
This is Capt... uh Lieutenant Sosa. ls this Agent Lynch?
不好意思  我不知道你的名字
I'm sorry, I don't have a first name.
我也不知道  有何贵干  中尉
Neither do I. So, what can l do you for, Lieutenant?
我看见一张你在卡森要塞
I'm looking at an image of you
训练营的照片
from the disciplinary barracks at Fort Carson.
真性感
She's hot.
你在监狱里探访过前上校汉尼拔・史密斯吗
Did you visit former Colonel Hannibal Smith in prison?
我不知道你在说什么  前上尉
I don't know what you're talking about, former Captain.
林奇特工  如果是你协助史密斯逃走
Agent Lynch, if you facilitated Smith's escape
并且正在暗中协助和支持他的话
and are currently aiding and abetting him...
那可真是
Ooh. Buddy.
要是换作是你  这么做的话
lf you can make something like that stick,
可就一步登天了啊
your next promotion should be in the five-star range.
如果你还要协助他们抢回模板
And if you're helping to retrieve those engraving plates,
那我就不得不出手阻止你了
I'm going to have to go out of my way to disappoint you.
查出她的电话  电脑和其它辅助设备
I want her phones, her computers, any support packages she operates.
我要掌握一切  我要拦截她的所有情报
I wanna know everything. I want active intercept taps on everything she's got.
从现在开始监视她的一举一动
l want every move monitored from this moment forward.
她可是国防部的人
You realize she's DoD.
她是天王老子我也不怕  照做
I don't care if she's G-O-D. Do it.
长官  看看这个
Boss, check this out.
这张照片上  帕克是在法兰克福的孔希斯银行
We've tracked this photograph of Pike to the K?nigsbank in Frankfurt.
监控录像记录了上个月
Our surveillance has him and an unknown Arab
他一直和一个阿拉伯人一起
making regular trips from the train station to the bank
从火车站到银行去
all over the last month.
-帕克大意了  -要是我们查到了
- Pike's getting sloppy.  - Yeah, but if we're onto him,
史密斯那伙人会不会也盯上了他们
what are the odds that Smith and his team are onto Pike and the Arab, too?
不  不  这是国防部的高度机密信息
No, no, no, this is a direct pull-down from the Pentagon's database.
史密斯他们绝不可能得到这情报
There's absolutely no way Smith and his team could have this stuff.
不要低估他们  他们的情报远比我们得要多
I think we should assume they have more information than us at all times.
帕克自上个月以来  就一直把模板
Pike has been moving the stolen engraving plates
往法兰克福的孔希斯银行大楼运送
to the Konigsbank Tower in Frankfurt over the past month.
明天是最后一批箱子
Tomorrow, the last of the cases containing these plates
之后将转交给阿拉伯人
will be transferred to the Arab.
这是过去六个月来
This will mark the only time in the last six months
这些模板第一次集中出现
that all of the plates have been in one location.
要夺回它们  这是最好也是唯一的一次机会
It's our best and only shot at getting them back.
他们离开孔希斯银行大楼  乘坐七点一刻到苏黎世的火车
They leave the Konigsbank Tower for the 7:15 train to Zurich.
先生们  我们可不能让他们如愿了
Gentlemen, we're gonna make sure they miss that train.
-小白  -在
- Face?  - Yeah.
去找你的旧爱吧
Time to bring in your former flame.
要是她真如我所料那般犀利
If she's as good as l think,
现在就该去法兰克福了  为了拦截那些模板
then she'll be on her way to Frankfurt to intercept those plates.
-你为何要关照她  -她是个理想主义者
- Why would you tip her off?  - She's a crusader,
也许我们之后会用得到她
and we're gonna need her teed up at some point.
提高警惕  伙计们
Keep your eyes and ears open, boys.
查瑞莎・索萨
Charissa Sosa...
问题在于
Now the wrinkle.
要是索萨盯上了我们  也就可以推测  林奇也盯上了她
If Sosa's onto us, we can assume that Lynch is onto her.
要是林奇觉得她是个麻烦人物
And if he thinks she stands beteen him and those plates,
他就会毫不犹豫地干掉她
he won't hesitate to kill her.
小白  去火车站
Face, get to the train station.
我是索萨
This is Sosa.
要是林奇威胁到她  你要负责搞定
If there's a threat from Lynch, deal with it.
喂
Hello?
可以开枪  重复一遍  可以开枪
Shoot is green. Say again, shoot is green.
喂
Hello?
不对劲
Something's wrong.
我们成了靶子  快撤  这情况不妙
We're marked, guys. Pull back. I don't like this at all.
记住  别被人看到
See. Don't be seen.
-你好  美人儿  -你真够胆
- Hello, beautiful.  - You have got some balls.
-居然丢给我个手机  -没办法
- You put a drop phone on me?  - l had to, babe.
只有这样我才能跟你说话  林奇掌握着你所有的通讯线路
It's the only way I could talk to you. Lynch has all your comm lines.
-你都快撤掉你的人  -我会找到你的  小白
- I want you to pull your team now.  - I'm gonna find you, Face.
不要跟她或其他任何人直接接触
But do not engage her or anyone else directly.
我先找到你再说吧
Not if l find you first.
别  好了  好了
Come on, all right... Okay. Okay.
往 这 儿 看
天啊
Ow! Ow! Jesus!
-你到底想怎么样  -救你命
- What the hell are you doing?  - Trying to save you!
查瑞莎
Charissa.
你知道我们是无辜的  你心里清楚
Come on, you know we're innocent. You know this.
你在撒谎  就像你在巴格达那样
You're lying. Like you lied in Baghdad.
我不知道  我对模板的事一无所知
I did not know. l knew nothing about the plates.
当时的确不知道
At that... At that time.
你谎话连篇
You are completely full of shit!
你就别一套一套的了
Will you stop selling yourself on that
当时明明是你骗了我
and avoiding the fact that you lied to me!
-明明是你骗我  -什么时候
- You're the one that misled me.  - When?
-得了  你想翻旧账吗  -不错
- Come on. You wanna go there?  - Yeah, let's go there.
你知道我是玩玩的  你也就想和我玩玩
You heard l was a player and you wanted to play.
但我开始变得认真了  你就慌了
And then l got serious and you freaked!
-我慌了吗  我才没有慌  -你慌了
- Oh, l freaked? l did not freak!  - Yes, you did.
你惊慌失措  然后落跑
You panicked and you ran.
想想吧  查瑞莎
Charissa, come on.
我可是联邦逃犯  你也知道我被通缉
I'm a federal fugitive. You know exactly how wanted I am.
你觉得我干嘛来法兰克福  来找老情人吗  才不是
You think I came to Frankfurt to hash out some old heartbreak? No!
我之所以来这儿  因为不是我们干的  我们是被人陷害
I'm here because we didn't do this. I'm here because we were set up.
我相信最终会真相大白  所以我来这里冒险
I'm here because, in the end, the truth is worth the risk.
就算你不信任我  我也相信你
And I believe in you, even if you don't believe in me.
天  我都忘了你原来这么美
God, I forgot how beautiful you are.
收好这部手机
Hold on to that phone.
我的老天
OH MY GOD!
他有枪
HE'S GOT A GUN!
就在那儿  他有枪
RlGHT THERE! HE'S GOT A GUN!
枪
A GUN!
真废柴
Sucker.
-见鬼  -派克在哪儿
- Oh, shit.  - Where's Peck?
别光是问  快去找他
Excellent question. Find him!
请保持镇静  从最近的出口离开
Please stay calm and go to the nearest exit.
孔希斯银行大楼
德国  法兰克福
三号通道见
Meet you up on corridor three.
三号报告  现在一切正常
Three to base. We're all clear at this time.
包裹安全后给我确认一下
Give me confirmation as soon as the package is secure.
我们要看到视频监视画面
We need a video feed.
好了  开始吧
Okay, let's dance.
各就各位  准备行动
Coming down. Positions, prepare to move.
像平时一样  跟紧我  先生
As always, stay close to me, sir.
正在关闭第十层
Closing off the 10th floor.
十层的人   我们需要支援
Tenth floor, we need backup.
回来
Get back! Get back!
我什么都看不见
l can't see anything.
头儿  情况如何
How we doing there, big man?
默多克  接好阿拉伯人
Murdock, here comes the Arab.
这是一个向左边中场的
And here's a long drive
长传远射
hit deep into left center field.
默多克杀了回来  他是背水一战  竟然接住了
Murdock's back, he's at the wall, and he makes the catch!
我喘不过气来了
I can't breathe.
这是个圈套
It's a trap!
皮特  我们需要支援
Pete, we need backup!
怪头  箱子丢了
B.A., I lost the case.
我受到攻击  准备撤离
I'm taking fire. I'm out of here.
怪头  快去拿回模板
B.A., get to those plates.
一群联邦政府人员已经对
Deutsche Federal is responding to explosions and shots fired
-孔希斯大楼的爆炸和枪击做出了反应  -赶快离开这里
- at the Konigsbank building.  - Get us out of this mess and get us
-赶去大楼那边  -遵命
- to that building as soon as possible.  - Yes, ma'am.
是你逼我的  拜库斯
You made me work for this one, Baracus.
没想到我会这么狼狈
I didn't think l was this out of shape.
真不走运
I am, unfortunately.
其他人呢
Where's the rest of the team, huh?
史密斯  派克  还有那个傻逼飞行员  他叫什么来着
Smith. Peck. That idiot pilot, the asshole. What's his name?
我要把你打得屁股尿流  拜库斯  看看你有什么能耐
I'm gonna take this one out of your ass, Baracus. Let's see what you got.
来啊  发什么愣  没力气了吗
Come on. What are you doing? What, are you tired?
我不想伤害你  老兄
I'm not gonna hurt you, man.
不  你伤不了我  等着挨揍吧
No, you're not gonna hurt me, I'm gonna hurt you.
-我不想杀了你  伙计  -你不想吗
- l don't wanna kill you, man.  - You don't wanna kill me?
你根本杀不了我  我要杀了你  拜库斯
You're not gonna kill me. I'm gonna kill you, Baracus.
我没在开玩笑  帕克
I'm not playing with you, Pike.
来吧  我有两把枪  记得吧  我是左撇子
Here we go, because I got two guns. I'm a lefty, remember that, right?
刚刚打斗的时候  枪已经上膛了吧
So, as soon as that hammer goes back, it's on.
我发誓  我做得出来
I swear to God, I'll do it.
你不是懦夫吧
You're not a coward, are you?
是不
Are you?
真难看
Whoopsy.
去你妈的
Damn!
-要搭车吗  大块头  -你救了我一命  老兄
- Need a ride, big fella?  - You're a life-saver, man.
我下不了手
I couldn't shoot him.
让开  趴下
Get out of the way! Get down! Get down!
这么多条子
Yeah, this is about the right amount of cops.
你真可爱  你应该庆幸周围都是人
That's cute. You're lucky there are people around.
不  亲爱的  你才应该庆幸
No, sweetheart, you're lucky.
你不热下再吃吗
You eat that cold?
我不讲究
Any way I can get it.
屋顶有处地方漏了
There's a leak in the roof.
好多处都漏了
There's a lot of them.
-他们回来了  -是的
- Is that them?  - I got it.
好吧  我没偷看过阿拉伯人
All right. Not a peep out of the Arab.
索萨当时在火车站
Sosa was at the train station.
-你见她了吗  -是的
- You saw her?  - Yeah.
你和她谈过了吗
Did you talk to her?
我别无选择  好吗  相信我
I had no choice, okay? Just trust me on that.
信你个头  一涉及到女人你就头脑发热
I trust you to make historically bad decisions
尽出昏招
as far as women are concerned.
你到底是怎么想的
What part of you is thinking at the moment?
林奇的人要杀她  我必须阻止
Lynch's men moved in on her and l had to react.
这不是你派我去的初衷吗
That's why you wanted me there in the first place...
是去阻止而不是去泡她
To stop them! Not to engage her!
只有先泡上了她  我才能去阻止他们
I couldn't do one without the other.
得了  我很怀疑
Please. Somehow I doubt that.
你干嘛这么生气  我们找回了模板
Hey. What are you so pissed about? We got the plates.
她也得到了情报
You wanted her teed up. She's teed up.
她知道我们没偷
She knows we didn't steal them.
她肯定急于查出真正的幕后黑手
She'll be thrilled to find out who did.
什么
What?
你一定知道
You had to know.
你一定知道  如果你留我一条命  这一刻迟早会到来
You had to know if you left me alive, that this was coming.
你怎么会不知道呢
How could you not?
你教会了我一切
You taught me almost everything I know.
汉尼拔  你认识这个人吗
Hannibal. You know who this is?
我们都认识
We all do.
莫里森
Morrison?
不是吧
Hell, no.
天啊
Jesus Christ.
不知道这算不算祝福  行动顺利  朋友
Not so sure that it is a blessing, but good hunting, my friend.
谢谢
Thank you.
你个贱人
You son of a bitch.
莫里森  真天杀的
Morrison? Holy shit.
你不是将军
You're not a general.
你把他怎么了
How could you do this to him?
你对得起我们吗
How could you do this to us?
你不配当将军
You know nothing about leading men.
我就知道  林奇如果协助我逃跑  那你肯定也有参与其中
I knew if Lynch helped me escape, you had to be part of it.
你和帕克利用模板和林奇达成协议
You and Pike were making a play on those plates with Lynch,
但你背叛了他
and you turned on him.
就像你背叛我们一样
The way you turned on us.
林奇本来就没把我们算在内
Lynch was never gonna cut us in.
他只是在利用我们
He was gonna use us.
为保险起见他才把你拉进来
He brought you on as insurance.
你就没想过  这是背叛了你的挚友吗
He never thought you'd betray your oldest living friend.
我只是先下手为强  汉尼拔  我是个战士
I just hit first, Hannibal. I'm a fighting man.
你是个骗子  叛徒
You're a liar and a traitor!
别废话了  杀了我
Then don't draw this out. Kill me.
好主意呀
That's a fantastic idea!
头儿  让我来
Bos, let me do this.
小白   我可不杀人
Face, I ain't killing nobody.
你不杀  我杀
You're not, Bosco. I am.
不管他说啥  别杀他  好吗
No matter what he says, do not kill him, okay?
不想看就别过头去
You guys don't wanna watch? Just turn your heads.
-我不赞成杀他  -我也很想杀了他
- I'm not gonna be party to it neither.  - I wanna kill the son of a bitch, too,
但他是我们的救命稻草
but he's our ticket out.
他终于不说疯话了  听他一回
He knows what he's talking about for once. Listen to him.
-小白  他是我们唯一的证人  -默多克
- Face, he is our only evidence.  - Murdock, Murdock...
-明白不  -我们现在都是他害的
- Do you understand?   - He put us here.
等他给我们做完证再崩了他
You can blow his head off after he testifies, okay?
他把一切都毁了
He's ruined it!
-好好想想你在做什么  小白  -好了
- Think what you're doing, Face.  -  All right.
-如果你不能  -够了 兄弟们
- If you can't handle it...  - Boys, enough.
够了  小白
Enough! That's enough, Face.
够了  退下
Enough! Step down!
大家都出去
Everybody outside
我来
I got him.
-还是让我干掉他吧  -小白  出去
- I don't want you to have to do it.  - Face, outside.
退下
Stand down, soldier.
小白  马上
Face. Now!
-真他妈愚蠢  -你没事吧  伙计
- Fucking stupid.  - You okay, man?
你知道莫里森伪装成阿拉伯人
You knew Morrison was masquerading as the Arab.
-为什么不告诉我  -我也不能百分之百肯定
- Why not share that?  - I wasn't 100% sure.
只有99%的把握吗
How about 99%?
你不觉得这很重要吗
Would you think it was worth mentioning then?
林奇  你到底在想什么
Lynch, what did you think?
你觉得我会当场杀了他吗
You think I'd just kill him on the spot?
我知道你不会  我相信你
I was certain of it. I still am.
你拿到模板了吗
Do you have the plates?
当然  不然我会打给你吗
I wouldn't be calling you if I didn't.
史密斯  归还模板  杀了莫里斯  你们就能洗清罪名
Smith, return the plates, kill Morrison, and reclaim your lives.
我要白宫  国务院
I want signed and authorized amnesty agreements
和三军参谋长联席会议
for myself and for each of my men.
所签署并授权的赦免令
From the White House, the State Department
给我和我的兄弟们
and the Joint Chiefs of Staff.
你听到了吗
You hear me?
再给我点时间
I'm gonna need a little more time.
要多久
How much?
目标时间倒计时
五分钟
Give me five minutes.
我等着
I'm waiting.
还不明白吗  汉尼拔
Don't you get it, Hannibal?
我们为他们打仗  流血  牺牲
We fight for them, we bleed for them, we die for them...
他们才不管我们死活
They don't give a rat's ass.
死亡和毁灭
Death and destruction,
对他们来说无足轻重
they're selling it like it was on the goddamn commodities exchange.
你别指责他们   和他们无关
Don't push this off on them. This is not about them.
你所谓的反战已经造成了数十亿美元的损失
Your war protest was stealing billions of dollars!
你到底是谁
Who are you?
我是将军  你是名上校
I am a general. You are a colonel.
我指挥  你行动
I say, "Jump," and you say, "How high?" End of story.
你该上路了
It is now.
我亲眼看到你在阿灵顿的墓碑
l saw your tomb at Arlington.
为国捐躯的军人均葬于此
你是为国捐躯的英雄
You died a national hero.
死了太便宜你
Death's too easy.
我们再也不想听什么谎言了
And the last thing we need now is another lie.
别这样  汉尼拔  你欠我那么多
Don't do this. Hannibal, please. You owe me that much.
是你欠我
You owe me!
你要去告诉世人  我们是无罪的
You're gonna tell them we're innocent.
你欠我的
You owe me.
汉尼拔  你们所为之而战的东西
Hannibal, it's meaningless.
根本毫无意义
What are you fighting for now, you and those boys?
你们的军衔和名誉
Your ranks? Your reputations?
都是狗屁
They're shit!
你们就是罪人
You're convicts!
不管有没有模板   你们都是联邦逃犯
Plates, no plates, you are federal fugitives,
等他们利用完了你  汉尼拔  照样把你丢弃
and when they're done with you, Hannibal, they just fucking burn you.
祖鲁一号  我是阔剑  准备行动
Zulu one, Zulu one, this is Broadsword, you're clear to engage.
阔剑  这名字你起的吗
"Broadsword." Did you come up with that?
好酷的名字   阔剑
That's awesome. "Broadsword."
阔剑
"Broadsword."
头儿  你会那样做吗
Boss, could you do that?
对我们
To us?
就像莫里森那样对我们
What Morrison did?
不  永远不会
No. Not in a million years.
是啊  但你却失算了
Yeah, but you didn't see it coming, though.
你什么时候就认出他来了
How long did you know it was him?
你们疯了吗
Are you guys crazy?
你本来就是疯子  但  小白  你在谴责汉尼拔吗
I know you are, but, Face, are you accusing him?
我宁愿被特警队乱枪打死也不会背叛你们
I'd rather face a firing squad than betray you boys.
自己人不要吵起来
Don't let this tear us apart.
至少现在不能吵
Not now.
我们现在要比任何时候都团结才行
Not when we need each other like no other time before.
快跑
Move!
酷毙了
Wow. That's awesome.
就像使命召唤里的场景  你觉得呢
That looks exactly like Call of Duty, doesn't it?
好了  要求是  禁止发布新闻
All right. Here's the deal. No press release.
不要当地法律机关和新闻媒体参与
Keep local law enforcement and media off-site.
设立4.8公里的隔离和禁飞区
Get a three-mile cordon, ditto the no-fly zone.
派一支清理小队过去把该死的模板找回来
Get an agency scrub team out there and get me the goddamn plates back.
德国警方已经把你手下所有人都监禁在了孔希斯银行大楼
The German police have your entire team in custody in the Konigsbank Tower.
那不是我的人  是史密斯他们的  我单干
I don't do teams, babe. That's Smith's bag. I'm strictly a solo act.
美 国 大 使 馆
我喜欢轻装出行
I like to travel light.
像忠诚这种东西  我可不带
Stuff like loyalty doesn't fit in the overhead bins.
我以为你和史密斯是同伙
I thought you and Smith were working together.
你错了
You thought wrong.
我们是有武器  但你也管不着
Yes, we have weapons. No, you may not wand us.
你想要做交易吗  那就提条件吧
If you want to deal, we can deal.
让我费尽心思使你一败涂地
How about l dedicate my immediate future
如何
to destroying yours?
你怎么不聪明一些
How about you get smart and start dealing
在别人出手之前  先下手为强呢
before somebody else does?
前任上尉
Former Captain.
除非你有像这样的文件
Unless you've got a piece of paper that looks exactly like this one,
不然这个不合作的麻烦家伙归我管
then this troubled young loner belongs to me.
我们走
Let's go.
他们到底怎么搞来的引渡令
How the hell did they get an extradition order?
抱歉  帕克  至少我们按规矩办事
Sorry, Pike. At least with me, there are rules.
中情局也有规矩  比你们更高级而已
CIA's got rules. Our rules are just cooler than yours.
-走  -林奇
- Go.  - You know, Lynch,
要是我把你关在这间屋子里  那可是做了一件大好事
if l could seal this room with you inside, l'd be doing the world a big favor.
那可不好
That's not nice.
是林奇干的  肯定是他
Lynch? Had to be.
离火近一些  弟兄们
Stay close to the fires, boys.
要是那架武装机还在附近  那也测不出我们的体热
lf that gunship is still around, it won't read our body heat.
林奇个傻逼  这么心急要干掉我们  根本没想要确定模板的位置
That idiot Lynch, so quick to kill us, didn't even bother locating the plates.
我们现在还能不用武力吗  怪头
Where do we stand on the non-violence now, B.A.?
你生气了吗  你是该生气
You pissed? You should be.
现在模板有屁用  只有莫里森能帮我们洗脱罪名
Who gives a shit about the plates? Morrison was the only way to clear us.
没有了莫里森  一切都无济于事
And without Morrison, we got nothing.
-我们怎么办  头儿   -我不知道  默多克
- What do we do, boss?  - I don't know, Murdock.
-我不知道  -我知道
- I don't know.  - I do.
林奇个混球  我想我知道怎么对付他了
This guy Lynch, I think I got him figured out.
-你有计划了吗  小子  -我们怎么离开这儿
- You got a plan, kid?  - How do we get out of here?
给我二十分钟先
Give me 20 minutes.
所以莫里森和史密斯那伙人都死了
So, Morrison's dead. Smith and his team are dead.
15分钟后我们就能找到印刷模板
Another 15 minutes or so, we locate those engraving plates.
你在幸灾乐祸吗
What is this? Are you gloating?
不  我是在打击你  谁让你们背叛了我
No, this is me beating you after you burned me.
-我们做了交易  记得吗  -我们没做交易
- We had a deal, remember?  - Not you and me.
-你  我  还有莫里森  -我不是直接和你交易
- You, me and Morrison.  - Not you and me, directly.
所以你俩自己密谋  把我排除在外
And you two collude and cut me out.
你在干嘛  真要在车里杀人吗
Hey. What are you doing? In the car?
要在车里杀人吗
Are we doing... Are we gonna do this in the car?
-你来杀吗  -不是  他来
- You doing this?  - He's gonna do it.
好吧  在这儿死真是不错
Way to go. That's brilliant, right there.
你要干嘛  他在干嘛  老天
What are you doing? What is he doing?
-天啊  -怎么样了  凯尔
- Jesus.  - How's it going, Kyle?
-你还好吧  -还好
- You all right?  - I'm good.
老兄  你好个鬼  你在干什么
Brother, you are far from good. What are you doing?
欧版消音器
It's a European silencer.
逆时针装消音器  你就那样拿枪吗
It's a suppressor. Counter-clockwise. You're holding a gun like that?
你以前也像这样拿枪吗  你居然能活到现在
You've held a gun like that before and you're still here?
真是奇迹
That's amazing.
-别指着我  -天啊  当作我最后的请求
- Don't point that thing...  - Jesus. Final request,
不要让这家伙开枪打我
don't let this guy shoot me, please.
如果让索萨知道我们还活着
So, if Sosa knows we're alive...
她就会相信莫里森也还活着
She'll believe Morrison is alive, too.
但愿林奇还在监听索萨的通讯线路
Let's just hope that Lynch still has Sosa's comm lines.
我是索萨
This is Sosa.
莫里森将军在我手里
General Morrison is in my possession.
什么  抱歉  我听不清  你是哪位
What? I'm sorry. l can't hear you. Who is this?
-还没干掉他呀  -不是吧
- Okay, this was not well thought out.  - No shit.
看着  我来教你怎么杀我
I mean, look at this. Am I to teach you how to kill me?
帮个忙  好吗  拿起枪管
Hey, do me a favor, all right? Put the barrel...
拿起枪管对准我的头
Put the gun flush to my head.
-确定吗  -对了  就是这儿
- Are you sure?  - There you go, right there.
-子弹会横穿过去吗  -在你先打伤其他人之前
- Is that going to go through?  - Before you hurt somebody besides me.
好了  我们没事了
There you go. We're okay. We're okay.
绝不要反铐住一个坐着的人
Never cuff a man in a seated position with his hands behind his back.
这样就看不到他的手了
Makes it impossible to see the hands.
太酷了
That was cool.
-你喜欢吗  -喜欢
- You like that?  - I like that.
非常喜欢
I like that a lot.
你还好吗  蠢货
Are you all right, you idiot?
-是的  这一下真带劲  -给他拷上手铐
- Yeah. It was a good hit.  - Please handcuff him.
我们还要手铐干嘛  不用了
We don't need to use them again. We don't need the cuffs.
你知道自己在和谁说话吗
Who are you talking to?
-布拉德  要手机还是要枪  选一个  -天啊
- Brad, phone or gun.  - Jesus.
手机还是枪  选一个
Phone or gun. Pick.
-把枪放下  -我没有背叛你  是莫里森的主意
- Put the gun down.  - Hey, l didn't burn you. Morrison did.
我真想打死你
l really wanna shoot you.
你得听这个电话  长官
You gotta hear this, sir.
你是史密斯吗
Is this Smith?
前上校打给前上尉  真有趣
From a former colonel to a former captain,
我知道大约三十秒你就可以锁定信号
I know I've got about 30 seconds before you lock this signal.
所以听着  我们可以证明自己的清白
So listen, we can prove our innocence.
好吧  慢点说
Okay. All right. Now, go back.
你刚说你抓了莫里森将军吗
Did you say you have Morrison? You have General Morrison?
-是的  -他还活着吗
- Correct.  - You have him alive?
好得很  所以林奇想杀我们灭口
And well, despite Lynch trying to wipe us out wholesale.
电话里说不清  但莫里森的证词可以证明我们清白
Too much to explain now but Morrison's testimony frees us
揭发林奇的罪行
and fries Lynch.
没有模板可不行
Well, not without the plates.
也在我这儿
Also in mypossession.
记住  林奇以为我们已经死了  不要让他知道
Remember, Lynch thinks we're dead, and I want to keep it that way.
-好的  成交  -给我支笔
- All right. We'll deal.  - Give me a pen.
-何时何地  -给我支笔  有谁有笔吗
- Where and when?  - Got a pen? Anybody got a pen?
-洛杉矶码头  四十八小时后的凌晨  -你还用笔呀
- LA docks, 48 hours, dawn.  - You still use a pen?
我把莫里森和模板带来
I deliver Morrison and the plates.
作为回报  我要求在民事法庭上重审
In return, I want a retrial in front of a civilian court.
好  成交
All right. We'll deal.
洛杉矶码头  四十八小时后见
LA docks, 48 hours from now.
你们若敢耍花招  交易就取消
Any bullshit from your end, and that's it, deal's off.
-找到他了吗  -没有
- Did we get him?  - No.
帕克
Pike.
你相信有第二次机会吗
You believe in second chances?
现在相信了
I do now.
说太多了吗
Too much?
还好  差点就被定位了
I thought you were spot-on.
该我了
My turn.
小白来电
收好这部手机
Hold on to that phone.
我是索萨
This is Sosa.
你好  美人儿
Hello, beautiful.
谢谢
Thank you.
他们这下原形毕露了  看怪头那样
They got the raw end of the deal, didn't they? Look at B.A.
跟个大香蕉似的
He looks like a huge banana.
早上好  朋友
Good morning, my friend.
早上好
Good morning.
你是宾基・拉宾诺维兹神父吗
Rabbi Binky Rabinowitz?
见鬼  我给错护照了吗
What passport did I give you?
你从坦桑尼亚来的吗  我妈妈也是坦桑尼亚人
You're from Tanzania. My mother is from Tanzania.
-见鬼  -这什么情况
- Oh, shit.  - What the hell happened?
-让非洲人信犹太教  -这里是六号岗台
- ...converting Africans to Judaism. - This is station six...
我就是做这些事
Stuff like that.
准备行动  我右边有三个
Let's get ready to move. There's three to my right.
后面有两个  东北出口有一个
There's two behind me and one at the northeast exit.
等等
Wait a sec.
祝好
Shalom.
-他在干嘛  -默多克  正在编他的生平事迹
- What's he doing? - It's Murdock. Telling his life story.
上帝在我心
There is a God.
-你会说斯瓦希里语吗  -你不会吗
- You speak Swahili?  - You don't?
接下去有的忙了吗  小子
You got enough to work with, kid?
好吧
We will.
咱现在选择穿过大西洋
You and l have some major favors moving across the mid-Atlantic right now.
到一艘做黑市交易的深海货船上去
It's a deep-sea freighter, shipping strictly black-market merch.
我们怎么离开呢
How do we get out to her?
我说的就是一艘普通的旧船
A boat. A plain old boat.
默多克  坐船渡海  太帅了
This is what I'm talking about, Murdock. Traveling the open seas in style.
我就喜欢这种交通工具  没的比  船这么安全
This is the way l like to travel. classy-like. The way people used to, safe.
还坐什么飞机
We don't need a plane.
博斯克  但愿有一天我们能帮你克服飞行恐惧症
You know, Bosco, hopefully one day we'll get you over your fear of flying.
什么
What?
这原来不是船呀
Hey, that ain't a boat!
只是今天还不行
Just not today.
默多克  给我记住
Murdock, don't you remember what l said?
-你得自己背他过去了  -你得自己背他过去了
- I said you have to catch him...  - You have to catch him...
-你把他弄昏了之后  -你把他弄昏了之后
- ...after you inject him.  - ...after you inject him.
我错了
My bad.
见鬼  我的头痛死了
Damn it! My head, man.
-你最爱的椰奶咖喱橄榄沙司哟   -快给我  傻蛋
- Coconut- curry tapenade, your favorite.  - Give me that, fool.
吐司呢
You get them toast points?
给  吐司这就来了
Voila! Toast points.
你非得又把我弄晕吗
Y'all knocked me out again, huh?
听好  把你弄昏的是
Okay, now, the whole injection, knocking out,
汉尼拔和小白
Hannibal and Face.
而我是给你做咖喱橄榄沙司滴
The curry tapenade, Murdock.
但我明明是脸朝地摔倒的
Why do l feel like l fell on my face?
还骗我
Huh? Tell me that.
林奇是个矛盾体
Lynch is a paradox.
默多克  你发现了吗
Murdock, you done with that?
他本该匿名工作  却偏喜欢受人关注
This is a guy who needs anonymity, but he loves theatricality.
他是个行政官员  不是个执行者
He's an administrator, he's not an operator.
在哪儿
Where is it?
漂亮
Very nice.
所以他总是尽力远离现场
So he stays as far away from the point of impact as possible,
绝不会直接参与进去
and never gets his hands dirty if he can help it.
但我们要改变现状
But we're gonna change all that.
你骗不了一个职业骗子
You can't hustle a hustler, fool.
这玩意不能靠近火星和火苗  甚至闪光灯都不行
No sparks, no flames, not even a flashlight near this stuff.
慢点
Easy, easy.
这家伙绝不会出现在事发现场
This guy is never at the flashpoint of anything.
而是在幕后高枕无忧地暗中操纵
He's safe and sound somewhere, pulling the strings.
妈妈
Mama. Mama.
头儿  为什么搞得这么麻烦
Hey, boss. Why so many of these damn things anyway?
因为乱花渐欲迷人眼  伙计
Because overkill is underrated, my friend.
所以我们要揭开那家伙的保护茧
So we're gonna bring this guy down to ground level.
妈妈
Mama. Mama.
林奇  这边
This way, Lynch. Lynch.
他最害怕的一点
The last place he'd ever want to be.
就是自己在众目睽睽下被揭露真面目
Then you put him on display for the whole world to see.
还有问题吗
Any questions?
怎么了  头儿
What's up, boss man?
怪头
Hey, B.A.
这次任务艰巨吧
It's gonna get heavy, isn't it?
这我也说不好
Well, I can't promise you it won't.
给你读个东西  就一句
Let me read you something real quick.
以暴力取胜  意味着失败
"Victory attained by violence is tantamount to defeat,
因为这只是短暂的胜利
"for it is momentary."
甘地
Gandhi.
若是心中存在暴力  就把它发泄出来
"It is better to be violent if there is violence in our hearts,
这要胜过用非暴力来掩饰心中的脆弱
"than to put on the cloak of non-violence to cover impotence."
这是谁说的
Who said that?
还是甘地
Same guy.
甘地从不惧怕为自己的信仰而战
Gandhi wasn't afraid to fight for the things he believed in.
你又信仰什么  怪头
What is it you believe in, B.A.?
人生如戏
For life is but an opera
跑调了  是不
It's off, isn't it?
应该唱得更高点是吧
I think it's higher.
还不错了
No, it's good. It's not that, Murdock.
小白  怎么了
Face, what's wrong? Come on, man.
我也不知道  只是在想
l don't know, man. I'm just thinking past this.
这一路上  我们每次都能全身而退
You know, we've always come back alive,
都亏了老家伙的巧妙计划
the four of us, 'cause of the old man.
-我知道  -但我不是他
- l know.  - I'm not him.
小白  我知道
Face, l know this.
默多克  我不是汉尼拔
Murdock, I'm not Hannibal.
这次行动谁的牺牲会最大
Who has the most to lose on this, Face?
是我
Me.
但我相信你
And I trust you.
我明白
Yeah, l know,
但是  你就是个疯子
but you're crazy.
还没那么疯
Not that crazy.
洛杉矶港
西汉堡号
所有目标差不多到了
Our eagles may have landed.
大家准备好了吗
Everybody ready to roll?
收到  第一小队准备行动
Copy Team one on the move.
收到  第二小队按计划行事
Acknowledged. Team to en route.
好啦  大家准备好了吗
All right, guys, everybody ready?
好戏就要开幕了
Curtain's about to come up.
演出开始
Show time.
史密斯就在那里  盯紧他
That's Smith right there. Watch him.
所有小队都到位了吗
Ground team is in position?
准备就绪
Standing by.
已经就位
In position.
一队狙击手就位
Shoot Team One. Affirmative.
一号观测员  10到8点钟方向
Spotter One. 10-8.
注意听好了
Let's chattermark on comms for now.
莫里森是首要目标  模板就在集装箱里
Morrison's the primary tango. Plates are the package.
好了  他在跟索萨通话  把电话转过来
Okay, okay, he's talking to Sosa. I want this call.
你骗我们  我们说好的
You lied to me, Sosa. We had a deal.
快把那该死的电话转给我  谢谢
I want that goddamn call in my... Thank you.
是说好了  但我改了主意
We had a deal, but I'm changing the deal.
耍我吗  索萨
Are you kidding me, Sosa? Are you kidding me?
情况起了复杂的变化  现在不由你了
This is a complicated exchange and you have no play here.
听着  不然就一辈子
Listen, or remain at-large fugitives
-继续做你的通缉犯  -哦 不
- for the foreseeable future.  - Uh oh. No! No, no.
行行好  我已经把莫里森和模板带来了
For God sakes, I've got Morrison here and the plates.
我已经暴露了  索萨  暴露了
I'm exposed, Sosa. Exposed!
我们不在码头上交易
We're not doing this on the docks.
给我听好了  我们绝不会自首
Now listen to me, we're not turning ourselves in.
Now you listen to me, we're not turning ourselves in.
你必须按我的条件来  不然就没的谈
I need you to do it on my terms or nothing at all.
去你妈的  见鬼去吧  索萨
To hell with that, and to hell with you, Sosa!
她背叛了他
Ah. She burned him.
小白  怪头  我们撤  索萨耍了我们
Face, B.A., we're bugging out. Sosa's jammed us.
默多克  放下十号位的箱子
Murdock, get the chopper down here in 10.
他在转移他
Okay, he's moving him.
盯紧他  他要转移了
You got him? He's moving him.
老天爷  你别紧张
For the love of God, relax.
我没紧张  在转移了
I am relaxed. He's moving him.
不要这样  汉尼拔  求你了
Don't do this. Hannibal, please.
-那儿  莫里森就在那儿  杀了他  -等下  他拿了模板吗
- That's Morrison, right there. Take him.  - Wait, does he have the plates?
模板在史密斯手里  快行动
Smith has the plates. Go now.
-干掉他  他就在那儿  开枪  -我来搞定莫里森  准备射击
- Take him, he's right there. Kill him.  - I've got Morrison, taking a shot.
刚刚真险  小子
A little too close for comfort, kid.
刚才怎么了
What just happened?
天杀的他究竟想干嘛
What the hell is he doing?
他们人呢  谁来告诉我
Where are they? Somebody talk to me.
见鬼  那东西把他们压死了吗
Come on, did that thing crush them or what?
好吧  玩三个塑料杯可比这个简单多了
This was a hell of a lot easier when it was just three plastic cups.
大家冷静下来  提高警惕  不要鲁莽
Everybody just be cool. Pay attention. No hasty moves.
要打败林奇那样的人  有三个关键要素
So, you beat a guy like Lynch by drawing him in with three things.
奇了怪了  他们到底要干嘛
What the hell are they doing?
声东击西
Distraction.
到底怎么回事
Whoa, whoa, whoa! What is happening?
调虎离山
Diversion.
这是要调虎离山  别乱  目标在集装箱里
This is a diversion! Stay eagle on those containers.
他们要借此逃跑  快开火
They're breaking for the exits! Open fire!
不要暴露  回撤
Do not engage! Back off!
地面队伍  开枪
Ground teams, engage!
他妈的
Holy shit!
地面队伍  开枪
Ground team, re-engage.
你被史密斯耍了  他是想要
You are being played by Smith.
吸引你的注意力  林奇  放聪明点
He's trying to draw your eye line, Lynch. Come on, be smart.
抓住他  抓住他  快去
Take them! Take them! Take them! Take them!
注意塔身还有塔腰  是派克和拜库斯
Contact! Tower house and bow! It's Peck and Baracus!
还要能全身而退
And division.
这是个陷阱  快撤退
It's a trap! Pull back! Pull back!
-他妈的快离开那儿  -不
- Get the hell out of there!  - No, no, no.
这是怎么了  到底怎么回事
What is happening? What is going on?
这计划不错  小子
Nice one, kid.
是派克和拜库斯
It's Peck and Baracus!
-快开枪  -闭嘴  我知道该怎么做
- Shoot them!  - Shut up! l know what I'm doing.
够了  小朋友们  该我上了
Okay, paintballers, time to go pro.
怪头  执行下一步计划
B.A., get to your secondary position.
好了  扭转局面的人来了
Okay. Game-changer.
你们该适可而止了
Here's what l think of your best-laid plans.
妈的
Shit!
我的天呐
Jesus Christ!
伟大战略家史密斯的计谋就到此终止了
So much for the grand scheme, Smith.
他妈的到底怎么了
What the hell was that?
怎么回事  小白
Face, what the hell was that?
他给船身开了个窟窿
Pike hit the ship with a SMAW! He punched a hole in the hull!
那计划怎么办
What about the plan?
帕克把计划给搞乱了  这是意外状况
Pike just blew up the plan! We are ad-libbing!
博斯克  快走
Bosco, get out of there!
我去找汉尼拔
I'm going for Hannibal.
-掩护我  我去找模板  -遵命
- Cover me. I'm going for those plates.  - Yes, sir.
船要沉了  快走
The boat is going over! Get out of there!
抓紧
Bos, hang on!
天呀
Oh! Jeez!
靠
Shit.
博斯克  帕克占据有利位置  我快没子弹了
Bosco, Pike's got the high ground. I'm running low on ammo, man.
妈的
Shit!
怎么了  帅哥
How are you doing, handsome?
你的枪还他妈能使吗
Shit, can you cycle that weapon. Nice work.
战友和子弹
Jeez, close friends and bullets.
最需要他们的时候都去哪儿了呢
Where are they when you need them?
我和你没私仇  但看着这儿
Don't take this too personally, but look here,
笑一笑  等着枪响
smile, wait for the flash.
拜库斯
Baracus.
博斯克
Bosco!
林奇
Lynch.
来吧  林奇
Come on, Lynch.
林奇
Lynch.
出来吧  史密斯  别装神弄鬼了
Come on, Smith! Stop bullshitting.
来呀  林奇
Lynch. Come on, Lynch.
林奇
Lynch...
你找得到我吗
Where am l?
来呀  林奇
Come on, Lynch.
林奇
Lynch.
来找我吧  林奇
Where am l, Lynch?
来呀  林奇
Come on, Lynch.
林奇  林奇
Lynch, Lynch, Lynch, Lynch.
林奇
Lynch!
终于找到你了  汉尼拔  你可真难找
There you are, Hannibal. Been looking all over for you.
别以为我是白面小生
Hey, don't let the scarf fool you.
我的泰拳还有两下子  柔术还更好一点呢  但是
My muay Thai is pretty good. My jujitsu is a little better, but...
我手上这些功夫  比起那些集装箱啊车啊爆炸啊
You had this whole sleight-of-hand thing going with the containers
装神弄鬼啊什么的  还真是小巫见大巫
and the cars, and the fireworks. "Lynch, Lynch, Lynch!"
真他妈烦人  但老天给了帕克一个火箭筒
God, that's annoying. But you give Pike a rocket.
你没想到吧
There's your monkey wrench.
汉尼拔  别这样
Hannibal, don't do this.
你知道吗  史密斯  本来一切都照你的计划进行
You know, Smith, you could have the best recipe in the world...
-你欠我这么多  -可惜你千算万算
- You owe me that much.  - ...but you drop a few bullets
-漏算一着  -汉尼拔  别这样
- into the batter...  - Hannibal, don't do this.
-林奇  不要  -汉尼拔  别
- Lynch, no!  - Hannibal, please.
天
Oh, God.
天不遂人愿
...and that cake don't bake.
人证物证  都齐了  这下你有麻烦了
Uh-oh. Your witness, your gun, your problem.
你也算报效祖国了  抱歉
You served your country well. Excuse me.
好久不见  钱先生  我可等死你了
Hello, Ben, where have you been all my life?
汉尼拔  看看  两成年男子对决
Look at us, Hannibal. Couple of grown men.
你流血了  你居然流血了
I'm bleeding. You're bleeding.
别起来
Don't get up.
操你妈
God damn it!
你的泰拳和柔术都那么差劲  林奇
Your muay Thai is as bad as your jujitsu, Lynch.
你必须靠枪才行
Better stick with a gun.
要是有把装弹的枪你就死定了
You put a loaded weapon in my hand, I'll put a bullet in your head.
我说过我会杀了你
I told you l would shoot you.
防弹衣救了你一命
Kevlar saved your life.
问题是  要是瞄准你的头  这玩意还顶个球用
Thing is, it doesn't do much good if I pop you in the head.
我要能与防弹衣合为一体的话可就不一定了
It does if you melt it down.
汉尼拔  别这样
Hannibal, don't do this.
-汉尼拔  别  -要打败林奇那样的人
- Hannibal, please.  - So, you beat a guy like that
有三个关键要素
by drawing him in with three things.
-声东击西  -怎么回事
- Distraction.  - Whoa, whoa, whoa! What is happening?
调虎离山
Diversion.
全身而退
And division.
在众目睽睽下揭露他的真面目
Then you put him on display for the whole world to see.
搞毛
What the...
真不错
That's good.
真令人惊讶
Surprise.
布里斯特工
Agent Burress.
你叫我什么
What did you call me?
文斯・布里斯特工  不是你的名字吗
Agent Vance Burress? lsn't that your name?
至少我的逮捕令上是这么写的
At least that's the name I've got on this warrant here,
除非你有和这张一模一样的
and unless you have a piece of paper that looks exactly like...
真好笑  这是我曾说过的话
That's funny. That's what l said.
以我之道还施我身
She's quoting me.
慢慢来
Easy, easy.
你被捕了  罪名是蓄意制造虚假谋杀
You're under arrest for attempted murder,
以及盗窃政府最高机密的
violations of the Civil False Claims Act,
美钞模板
and the theft of top secret government engraving plates.
慢慢起来
Easy.
看来这计划还算顺利
l guess the plan went okay,
只是我没考虑到帕克会把船给炸了
considering Pike did blow up the boat, which l didn't account for at all.
子弹没打穿呢
Bullets didn't go through.
伙计  觉得怎样
How are you feeling, man?
不好  很不好
Not... Not good.
-怎么了  -不舒服
- What's wrong? - Not good.
我感觉精神正常了
I feel sane.
早知道我早该往你脑袋上来一枪
I should have shot you in the head a long time ago.
我怎么觉得你害怕了
Is it crazy that I'm feeling your anxiety right now?
我看起来像害怕的样吗
Do I look anxious to you?
你觉得我被打败了吗
You think I'm beaten?
我只是在流血  没有流虚汗
I'm bleeding, l'm not sweating.
把他带走
Let's take him out of here, guys. Go ahead, princess.
脑震荡和撞伤有什么区别吗
What's the difference between a concussion and a contusion?
-没事的  伙计  -默多克  干得不错
-It don't matter, bro. You tore up.  - Murdock, that was beautiful.
你没事  头盔很有用嘛
You were right. The helmet worked.
番茄酱立功了
Ketchup worked great.
你表现真棒  现在感觉怎么样
You did a great job. You okay?
-还好  -清醒点了吗
- Yeah.  -  Got your bell rung?
下次还是让汉尼拔制定计划吧
Just let Hannibal make the plans next time.
-好吧  -好吧
- Oh. Okay.  - Okay.
你的良心感觉怎么样  大块头
How's the conscience, big guy?
平静如水
At peace.
别熄火
Keep it turning.
我们要带走他们
We already got them on the exits.
现在方圆3公里都被封锁了  -索萨是哪位
- We got a two-mile no-fly zone here.  - Which one of you is Sosa?
-我是  -我要找索萨
- I am. I am. - I need to talk to Sosa.
从现在开始  你的囚犯将遣回
As of right now your prisoner is to be remanded
-联邦关押  -我有他的逮捕令
- into federal custody.  - l have a warrant for this man.
-现在  -我来告诉你吧  我是医生
-  As of right now...  - I'll tell you what... I'm a doc.
让我来治疗你  我来帮你
Let me doctor you up. Let me help you out.
你要缝针吧
Do you need stitches? Please tell me you need stitches.
我会帮你缝得很好哟
l can stitch you up really good.
先生们
Gentlemen.
中情局
The Central lntelligence Agency
秉持高度的伦理道德
believes in and evinces a profound moral ethic,
和坚定不移的职业标准
as well as an unshakeable professional standard.
因此  我们为发生的一切
As such, we would like to extend our most sincere apologies
向你们表达最诚挚的歉意
for what's happened here.
-祝你们好运  -你们要带他去哪里
- Good day and God bless.  - Where are you taking him?
你说谁
Who?
我不知道你的名字
I never got your name.
我叫林奇
My name is Lynch.
果然
Of course it is.
他刚刚是说林奇吗
Did he just say Lynch?
别碰我
Hey. Do not touch me.
别紧张  伙计们
Take it easy, guys.
所有人都给我退下
Everybody, stand down! Stand down!
-去把拿上模板  -所有人给我退下
-Get those plates. - Everybody, stand down!
-这是命令  给我退下  -你想干什么
- That's an order. Hey, you, stand down. -  What is wrong with you?
中尉
Lieutenant.
长官  你是几时到的  我不知道
Sir, when did you arrive? l had no idea...
-给我点时间  -遵命
- Just give me a minute.  - Yes, sir.
把你的手拿开  肌肉男
FACE: Get your hands off me, tough guy.
虽然搞得一团糟  但我们好歹拿回了模板
Well, that's one hell of a mess. But we did get the plates.
但不幸的是  我得以逃脱合法监禁的罪名控告你们
Unfortunately, I'm gonna have to charge you all with escaping lawful custody.
什么  汉尼拔  那家伙在说什么
What? Hannibal, what is this guy talking about?
怪头  虽然是误判  但我们越狱还是违法的
B.A., we were wrongly convicted, but it's still illegal to break out ofjail.
长官  史密斯他们为这次行动
Director McCready, Smith and his team
立下汗马功劳
were instrumental in recovering those plates.
但他们仍是十级通缉犯  必须逮捕他们
They're still level-10 federal fugitives and l need that off my desk.
这真他妈扯淡  长官
This is chickenshit, sir.
也许对他们是很扯淡
Yeah, well, you know what? Perhaps for them, it is chickenshit,
但是对你  上尉  我们决定将你重新升为上尉
but for you, Captain, we're re-promoting you to your former rank.
他们马上会被转移
So, look, they're gonna be delivered
交给长滩市的联邦法警
to the U.S. Marshals Service here in Long Beach.
-以最高的安全级别运走他们  -我理解  但
-And there should be a C-5 transport... -l understand, but...
半小时后起飞
...on the tarmac in half an hour.
-这势在必行  -这很不公平长官
- This needs to be done. - This is really unfair, sir.
-真他妈扯蛋  -我可是胡迪尼大师
- This is bullshit.  - I'm like Harry Houdini.
逃脱术大师
这手铐我很容易就能咬开
I chew through your cuffs.
-起身  前进  进去  -往前走
- Get up. Step up. Get in there!  - Step up!
-行动起来  -等下  停一下
- Let's go. Get moving. - Stop. Wait, stop.
-走  -等等
- Move it. -Wait.
-这太没道理了  -不用担心
- This is so wrong.  - It got a little aggressive.
-不用担心  -现在这样真的大错特错了
- Don't worry about it.  - This is really, really wrong,
我会不惜一切代价来弥补
and I'm going to do everything l can to fix it.
-我相信你  -我真的很抱歉  小白
- I know you will.  - I'm so sorry, Face.
这计划真不错  小白
Nice plan, Face.
好个毛  才抓住林奇  结果我们又进了监狱
Yeah. We just traded Lynches, and we're going back to prison.
我们交还了模板  这下能抬头做人了
We returned the plates. We can hold our heads high.
我们做了应该做的
We did the right thing.
但他们却这样对待我们  真他妈的
Yeah, and look what they did to us. This is some bullshit.
他们又抛弃了我们  汉尼拔
They burned us again, Hannibal.
我们相信国家机关  但他们却恩将仇报
We trusted the system and it turned on us.
记住  小子们  无论表面上看起来多么混乱
Remember, boys, no matter how random things might appear,
本质上总是有计划存在  小子
there is still a plan. Kid.
我不是故意抢你台词  头儿  不过
Well, l don't mean to steal your line, boss, but...
我就爱计划圆满的那一刻
I love it when a plan comes together.
依旧被政府通缉
Still wanted by the government,
但这些战士们  一次次地神奇逃脱
they survive as soldiers of fortune.
如果你遇到困难
lf you have a problem,
如果你走投无路
if no one else can help,
你要是能找到他们
and if you can find them,
或许就能雇佣
maybe you can hire
天龙特攻队
the A-Team.